<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://localhost:4000/assets/xslt/rss.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://localhost:4000/assets/css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Bitcoinfo</title>
		<description>Bitcoin is a little complicated. Bitcoinfo is meant to break down the varieties into a navigable structure.</description>
		<link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Why Bitcoin?</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/info/why-bitcoin/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/info/2020-01-02-why-bitcoin.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/info/2020-01-02-why-bitcoin.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;to-include-the-many-reasons&quot;&gt;…to include the many reasons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, the most important reason, is its deflationary nature, the fixed nature of its money supply, and that it’s decentralized to the extent that changing it is difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some other cryptocurrency efforts are interesting to me for other reasons. However, in my opinion, none of them solve this fundamental problem of global currencies in the way that Bitcoin does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pierre_rochard/status/988403000682139649&quot;&gt;Pierre Rochard (@pierre_rochard)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Why I’m focused on Bitcoin: • Schelling point consensus • p2p network governance with full nodes • proof-of-work secure timestamping • Lindy effect / first mover advantage • fixed issuance schedule • prudent engineering culture • promising research: lightni…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hackernoon.com/why-bitcoin-why-sooner-rather-than-later-e44aa5373479&quot;&gt;Why Bitcoin &amp;amp; why sooner rather than later? – Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This article was inspired by an investor of ours who was looking to present the case for bitcoin to his firms investment committee. I…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.xapo.com/why-own-bitcoin&quot;&gt;Why Own Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;1- Take 1% of what you have, and buy Bitcoin (all at once and at the market price) 2- Carry it at cost 3- Do not touch it for 10 years&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;central-banks-deflate-global-currencies-at-an-alarming-rate&quot;&gt;Central Banks Deflate Global Currencies at an Alarming Rate&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the United States, that began around the time the Federal Reserve was enstated, 1913.  They do this by creating dollars with no underlying value, but are treated the same as all other dollars in circulation. The immediate result is apparent prosperity, as was seen during the roaring ‘20. However, the crash is sure to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/a2/ce/21/a2ce2172d47f63711cfbdc5340eba4ea.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is a hedge against such practices, since previously, citizens had no other choice but to use their local currency. Outside of the US, many countries made use of even more extreme inflation than in the states. In those cases, global citizens have used US dollars, to opt out of their local failing currencies. However, that is just kicking the can down the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, shit rolls down hill, so private banks make use of similar practices, funneling wealth from the bottom to the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mises.org/library/what-has-government-done-our-money&quot;&gt;What Has Government Done to Our Money?&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;When this gem first appeared in 1963, it took the form of a small paperback designed for mass distribution.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Innumerable economists, investors, commentators, and authors have learned from this book through the decades. After fifty years, it remains the best book in print on the topic, a real manifesto of sound money.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Rothbard boils down the Austrian theory to its essentials. The book also made huge theoretical advances. Rothbard was the first to prove that the government, and only the government, can destroy money on a mass scale, and he showed exactly how they go about this dirty deed. But just as importantly, it is beautifully written. He tells a thrilling story because he loves the subject so much.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mises.org/library/origins-federal-reserve&quot;&gt;Origins of the Federal Reserve | Murray N. Rothbard&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The financial elites were responsible for putting through the Fed as a governmentally created and sanctioned cartel device to enable the nation’s banks to inflate the money supply in a coordinated fashion.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theinstitutionalriskanalyst.com/single-post/2018/06/09/Update-The-Financial-Repression-Index&quot;&gt;The Institutional Risk Analyst | Update: The Financial Repression Index&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Back in April we published a comment, “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theinstitutionalriskanalyst.com/single-post/2018/04/04/Bank-Earnings-Financial-Repression&quot;&gt;Bank Earnings &amp;amp; Financial Repression&lt;/a&gt;,” that introduced the concept of the Financial Repression Index.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;In a related working paper available on SSRN, “&lt;a href=&quot;http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3155370&quot;&gt;The Financial Repression Index: U.S Banking System Since 1984&lt;/a&gt;,” we define the index, which essentially shows the distribution of bank interest income between debt investors and bank shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MpG-r9FnnXY&quot;&gt;The Money Masters 1996 FULL DOCUMENTARY&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The Money Masters is a 1996 documentary film that discusses the concepts of money, debt, taxes, and describes their development from biblical times onward. -&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1954955/&quot;&gt;imdb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2nBPN-MKefA&quot;&gt;Money as Debt I - Revised Edition 2009 (Full Movie)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;-Debt - government, corporate &amp;amp; household has reached astronomical proportions.
-Where does all this money come from?
-How could there BE that much money to lend?
-The answer is… there isn’t.
-Today, MONEY IS DEBT. 
-If there were NO DEBT, there would be NO MONEY.
-If this is puzzling to you, you are not alone. Very few people understand even though ALL of us are affected.
-This fast-paced and highly entertaining animated feature by artist &amp;amp; videographer, Paul Grignon explains today’s magically perverse DEBT-MONEY SYTEM in terms that are easy to understand. - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/PaulLWGrignon/playlists&quot;&gt;original playlists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.moneyasdebt.net/&quot;&gt;Money as Debt&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;References and Resources for the animated short Money as Debt&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thefiscaltimes.com/Columns/2018/08/30/Idea-Fed-Independent-Absurd&quot;&gt;The Idea That the Fed Is ‘Independent’ Is Absurd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/NickSzabo4/status/1031231342803972096&quot;&gt;Nick Szabo 🔑 (@NickSzabo4)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;@ummjackson @jimmysong The Cantillon effect: “the first ones to receive the newly created money see their incomes rise whereas the last ones to receive the newly created money see their purchasing power decline as consumer price inflation comes about.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/glvGFWi&quot;&gt;https://t.co/glvGFWi&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/GoldTelegraph_/status/991791693199425536&quot;&gt;Gold Telegraph (@GoldTelegraph_)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Want to know why the USA will eventually be stripped as the reserve currency of the world? Just take a look at this:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MI_Investments/status/1028468590356250624&quot;&gt;M/I_Investments (@MI_Investments)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;StLouisFed: “Corporate profits and employee wages have tracked each other closely for decades—until the mid 2000s, when profits leaped out in front.”&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;️Let me see, we had the $2008 Financial Crisis, lost 9MM workers and then the US gov’t IOU’d $1.2T/yr for 9 yrs ($11…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/spectatorindex/status/1028362918142730240&quot;&gt;The Spectator Index (@spectatorindex)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Currency against US Dollar, past year. Venezuela: -2,000,000% Sudan: -168% Turkey: -67% Argentina: -65% Angola: -57% Iran: -30% Brazil: -21% Ethiopia: -18% Pakistan: -17% Russia: -13% Sweden: -12% Tunisia: -11% Nicaragua: -8% Indonesia: -8% Myanmar: -8% Haiti: -8% India: …&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cburniske/status/1033828237347106822&quot;&gt;Chris Burniske (@cburniske)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;1/ Just finished @andrewrsorkin’s “Too Big to Fail.” What a masterpiece in storytelling— a front row seat of the 2008 Financial Crisis.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coingape.com/bitcoin-2020-set-for-next-financial-crisis/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin: 2020 Set for Next Financial Crisis, Everything will Come Crashing Down&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;2020 has been set as the date for the next financial crisis by the economist and experts alike that will break down everything as JPMorgan chase details the crashing we will be seeing. What role Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies will play here?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hugohanoi/status/973693594128211968&quot;&gt;Hugo Nguyen (@hugohanoi)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;1/ Did you know, that the Vietnam war was a major contributor to the US going off the Gold Standard (aka the “Nixon shock”), which gave birth to the international fiat currencies system that we know today?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/PHe0bXAIuk0&quot;&gt;How The Economic Machine Works by Ray Dalio&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Economics 101 – “How the Economic Machine Works.” Created by Ray Dalio this simple but not simplistic and easy to follow 30 minute, animated video answers t…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://letstalkbitcoin.com/blog/post/what-bitcoin-did-36-an-interview-with-caitlin-long-saifedean-ammous&quot;&gt;What Bitcoin Did #36 An Interview with Caitlin Long &amp;amp; Saifedean Ammous&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Negative interest rates are purely a construct of the artificiality of the monetary system. There is going to a major bond crash - the challenge is that this could be years if not decades away, or it could be tomorrow.” — Caitlin Long&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@brucefenton/how-do-you-know-you-own-your-stocks-you-dont-so-who-has-the-ledger-262def52ae4&quot;&gt;How Do You Know You Own Your Stocks? You Dont. So who has the ledger?&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;(Part 3 of 4: The Present, How Value is Tracked and Settled)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intjr/status/1048098080388603905&quot;&gt;intjr (@intjr)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;@BobMcElrath @_tessr There were public discussions after 2009 fin crisis, 2010 Greek crisis, 2011 MF Global collapse. Tri-party repo, securities lending and rehypo of collateral are necessary for the functioning of the financial system, per Bill Dudley (former NYFed). http…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theinvestorspodcast.com/blog/americas-long-term-challenge-3-destruction-of-the-currency/&quot;&gt;America’s Long-Term Challenge #3: Destruction of the Currency&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If you look at the history of the US dollar, it has lost 98.5% of its value since 1792. What’s incredible about this constant, steady destruction of the currency is how subtle it is.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@alicheaib/the-u-s-federal-reserve-a-private-bank-owned-by-the-most-powerful-and-wealthiest-families-on-82b096544170&quot;&gt;How the U.S. Federal Reserve came to be and why it has to change&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“It is well enough that people of the nation do not understand our banking and monetary system, for if they did, I believe there would be a revolution before tomorrow morning.” ~ Henry Ford, founder of the Ford Motor Company.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stlouisfed/status/1047128315297972224&quot;&gt;St. Louis Fed (@stlouisfed)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The Triffin Dilemma refers to the double-edged sword of possessing a currency that serves as the world reserve currency. If a private cryptocurrency were to replace a given world reserve currency, this would eliminate the dilemma for that currency &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/NgzPLcWbMM&quot;&gt;https://t.co/NgzPLcWbMM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@brucefenton/how-do-you-know-you-own-your-stocks-you-dont-so-who-has-the-ledger-262def52ae4&quot;&gt;How Do You Know You Own Your Stocks? You Dont. So who has the ledger?&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;(Part 3 of 4: The Present, How Value is Tracked and Settled)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intjr/status/1047025983432343552&quot;&gt;intjr (@intjr)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;History is instructive.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://zerohedge.com/article/overview-feds-intervention-equity-markets-primary-dealer-credit-facility&quot;&gt;An Overview Of The Fed’s Intervention In Equity Markets Via The Primary Dealer Credit Facility&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://zerohedge.com/news/2012-10-01/everything-you-wanted-know-about-tri-party-repo-markets-were-afraid-ask&quot;&gt;Everything You Wanted To Know About Tri-Party Repo Markets But Were Afraid To Ask&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://zerohedge.com/news/shadow-rehypothecation-infinte-leverage-and-why-breaking-tyrrany-ignorance-only-solution&quot;&gt;Shadow Rehypothecation, Infinite Leverage, And Why Breaking The Tyranny Of Ignorance Is The Only Solution&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://zerohedge.com/article/rare-glimpse-feds-discount-window-courtesy-brewing-lehman-barclays-scandal&quot;&gt;A Rare Glimpse Into The Fed’s Discount Window Courtesy Of The Brewing Lehman-Barclays Scandal&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://zerohedge.com/news/why-uk-trail-mf-global-collapse-may-have-apocalyptic-consequences-eurozone-canadian-banks-jeffe&quot;&gt;Why The UK Trail Of The MF Global Collapse May Have “Apocalyptic” Consequences For The Eurozone, Canadian Banks, Jefferies And Everyone Else&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://newyorkfed.org/banking/tpr_infr_reform.html&quot;&gt;Tri-Party Repo Infrastructure Reform&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://imf.org/external/pubs/ft/wp/2010/wp10172.pdf&quot;&gt;The (sizable) Role of Rehypothecation in the Shadow Banking System&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://imf.org/external/pubs/ft/wp/2011/wp11256.pdf&quot;&gt;Velocity of Pledged Collateral: Analysis and Implications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/482031916506415116/508685602850603018/DoyHlV7WwAAUtoX.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macrovoices.com/mobile-home/464-keith-dicker-the-next-major-financial-crisis-will-happen-in-the-bond-market&quot;&gt;Keith Dicker: The next major financial crisis will happen in the B…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/updates/history-rothschild-family/&quot;&gt;A History of the Rothschild Family&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;A history of the Rothschilds, a prominent German family that established banking and finance houses in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@alicheaib/the-u-s-federal-reserve-a-private-bank-owned-by-the-most-powerful-and-wealthiest-families-on-82b096544170&quot;&gt;How the U.S. Federal Reserve came to be and why it has to change&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“It is well enough that people of the nation do not understand our banking and monetary system, for if they did, I believe there would be a…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pierre_rochard/status/1060214067351244800&quot;&gt;Pierre Rochard (@pierre_rochard)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;No cryptocurrency is a true unit of account or a payment instrument, and we have seen this year that they are a poor store of value. Buyers of cryptocurrencies are buying into nothing more than a software algorithm.” Agustín Carsten &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/Z39zAhf6i2&quot;&gt;https://t.co/Z39zAhf6i2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://offthechain.substack.com/p/the-dtccs-innovation-dilemma&quot;&gt;The DTCC’s innovation dilemma&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Join thousands of others who receive this daily analysis of crypto markets &amp;amp; news in their inbox every morning - subscribe now. Banks aren’t going to go down quietly. Rather than completely ignore blockchain and crypto, the intelligent financial organizations are scrambling…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptoslate.com/szabo-traditional-finance-destroyed-its-tradition-merit-of-crypto-over-fiat/&quot;&gt;Szabo: Traditional Finance Destroyed its Tradition, Merit of Crypt…&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;According to crypto pioneer Nick Szabo, the traditional finance sector has destroyed its tradition and has implemented inappropriately complex policies.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/LgI0liAee4s&quot;&gt;Escaping the Global Banking Cartel&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Expanding on an observation from his last talk, Andreas asks why we talk so much about the cartels in drugs and oil, but rarely about one of the largest cartels in the world: banking. He analyses recent (unacknowledged) history with the 2008 financial crisis, the corrupt revolving door&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stephanlivera.com/episode/40&quot;&gt;SLP40 Vijay Boyapati – Why Credit Deflation is More Likely Than …&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Vijay Boyapati (Software Developer, Austrian Economist) joins me to discuss his 2010 article, “Why Credit Deflation Is More Likely Than Mass Inflation”. Find out where economics comment…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gendal.me/2013/11/24/a-simple-explanation-of-how-money-moves-around-the-banking-system/&quot;&gt;A simple explanation of how money moves around the banking system&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Twitter went mad last week because somebody had transferred almost $150m in a single Bitcoin transaction. This tweet was typical: There was much comment about how expensive or difficult this would …&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@hasufly/why-bitcoin-3fdee2328759?sk=1239f34c3ee8a40116d38660ec91ae63&quot;&gt;An Honest Account of Fiat Money&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;A framework for Bitcoin skeptics, part 1&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/matt_odell/status/1068524052971577345&quot;&gt;Matt Odell (@matt_odell)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Trusted third parties are security holes. DoD: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/YPuFdT7rPF&quot;&gt;https://t.co/YPuFdT7rPF&lt;/a&gt; Deutsche Bank: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/Bc2dEdr1i3&quot;&gt;https://t.co/Bc2dEdr1i3&lt;/a&gt; Marriot: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/7rmQO1rG1y&quot;&gt;https://t.co/7rmQO1rG1y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/482031916506415116/537522361189007360/DuZFsQdWkAAQhQJ.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; [&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.americanbanker.com/news/is-this-swifts-answer-to-ripple&quot;&gt;Is this Swift’s answer to Ripple?&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Swift is showing more swagger in its rivalry with Ripple thanks to progress it has made with a multifaceted payments-tracking technology called GPI.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/_JustinMoon_/status/1077744645948538881&quot;&gt;Justin Moon (@&lt;em&gt;JustinMoon&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“In the absence of the gold standard, there is no way to protect savings from confiscation through inflation” - ALAN FUCKING GREENSPAN&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DyV0OfU3-FU&quot;&gt;Money vs Currency - Hidden Secrets Of Money Episode 1 - Mike Maloney&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;More: &lt;a href=&quot;http://hiddensecretsofmoney.com/&quot;&gt;http://HiddenSecretsofMoney.com&lt;/a&gt; Currency vs. Money is the 1st Episode of Mike Maloney’s Hidden Secrets of Money, a series presented by Mike Maloney as …&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/crypToBanger/status/1050078958182649857&quot;&gt;paTo.. 🌕 (@crypToBanger)&lt;/a&gt; – Huge Thread
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;i have no idea just trying to connect the ……. #everyThingbubbLe excepT #Bitcoin&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jonathanstray.com/the-origin-of-banking&quot;&gt;http://jonathanstray.com/the-origin-of-banking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ourenemythefed.com/&quot;&gt;Our Enemy, the Fed&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Beat back the propaganda about the Federal Reserve with this free eBook.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/StockTwits/status/1078689298931765250&quot;&gt;Stocktwits (@Stocktwits)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is the history of bull and bear markets. Hang it on your wall. $SPX $DJIA &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ABRW500mrh&quot;&gt;https://t.co/ABRW500mrh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://news.goldseek.com/GoldSeek/1192819378.php&quot;&gt;America’s Forgotten War Against the Central Banks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/yassineark/status/1139187096315408385?s=12&quot;&gt;Yassine Elmandjra (@yassineARK)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;In the last 100 years, three periods were followed by HALF of the world’s currencies losing HALF of their purchasing power: 1. 1913 creation of Federal Reserve (+ Europe’s WWI gold standard abandonment) 2. 1933 US gold standard suspension 3. 1971 US gold standard abandonm…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nlw/status/1140244886542831617?s=12&quot;&gt;Nathaniel Whittemore (@nlw)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Because I don’t assign you enough reading already, highly recommend @jfc&lt;em&gt;3&lt;/em&gt; finance history Sunday reads. Get that historical context, fam. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/kcAcHWAlxF&quot;&gt;https://t.co/kcAcHWAlxF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/482031916506415116/603439075571138576/image0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/482031916506415116/603439075571138576/image0.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/EileenAppelbaum/status/1119307516792512512?s=20&quot;&gt;Eileen Appelbaum (@EileenAppelbaum)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;THREAD: The retail apocalypse in full swing: Gymboree closes 800 stores, Shopko 105, Payless 2300, Charlotte Russe 400. What’s behind it? Some blame Amazon or changing taste, but the real culprit is private equity. We’ll explain how PE makes money as these businesses…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/csuwildcat/status/1155031205265301504?s=12&quot;&gt;Daniel Ƀ (@csuwildcat)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;That thing where the IMF declares its intent to drive everyone on Earth to use Bitcoin by openly stealing traditional banking deposits: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/O8NeFAr0AD&quot;&gt;https://t.co/O8NeFAr0AD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hartej_/status/1155031253495746560?s=12&quot;&gt;hartéj sawhney (@hartej_)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It makes me sad when seemingly smart, young people do not understand what capitalism is “The Morality of Capitalism” by @yaronbrook &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/KpOxKZzgI8&quot;&gt;https://t.co/KpOxKZzgI8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pierre_rochard/status/1158526886303162369?s=12&quot;&gt;Pierre Rochard (@pierre_rochard)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The Fed is not independent. Bitcoin is independent. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/WfbWF6y9Rd&quot;&gt;https://t.co/WfbWF6y9Rd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://people.stern.nyu.edu/adamodar/New_Home_Page/valuationtools.html#cf&quot;&gt;Corporate Finance Valuation Tools&lt;/a&gt;
this website has so much information&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=20701252&quot;&gt;The Population Bust&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hYzX3YZoMrs&quot;&gt;Why the whole banking system is a scam - Godfrey Bloom MEP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cryptoretreat/status/1175267997201494022?s=21&quot;&gt;crypto retreat (@cryptoretreat)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;/r/bitcoin: why bitcoin? this is why. a must watch. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3WclYu5l4G0&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&quot;&gt;The developed world is on the brink of a financial, economic, social and political crisis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/info/why-bitcoin/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Bitcoin Security Info + Best Practices</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/info/security/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jlopp/physical-bitcoin-attacks&quot;&gt;jlopp/physical-bitcoin-attacks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Known Physical Bitcoin Attacks&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;A list of known attacks against Bitcoin / crypto asset owning entities that occurred in meatspace. NOTE: this list is not comprehensive; many attacks are not publicly reported.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Readers may be interested in this relevant presentation: “&lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/365979416#t=24m50s&quot;&gt;The Hodlguard- a primer on physical security in Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;” and &lt;a href=&quot;https://prezi.com/view/P46hHguLiPvqA7aZ7gYR&quot;&gt;slides&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nongiach/awesome-cryptocurrency-security&quot;&gt;nongiach/awesome-cryptocurrency-security&lt;/a&gt;
Curated list about cryptocurrency security (reverse / exploit / fuzz..) - nongiach/awesome-cryptocurrency-security&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/crymeaCOIN/status/1055373440713142272&quot;&gt;justfive (pepefull for #FreeStardust) (@crymeaCOIN)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;0/ This is a thread with basic steps that you can take to secure yourself on a very basic level. Yes, these are very basic and there are ways that tech gurus go beyond that to secure themselves. It has also been done before so not much new here. Lets begin:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://btcmanager.com/making-bitcoin-transactions-untraceable-with-the-wasabi-wallet&quot;&gt;Making Bitcoin Transactions Untraceable with the Wasabi Wallet | B…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In the cryptocurrency ecosystem, a wallet is an essential component, as it is used to receive, send and store cryptocurrencies. It operates in the crypto verse just like the banks do in the traditional financial system. As the crypto sector is continuously growing with more a…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lopp/status/1080231724104044544&quot;&gt;Jameson Lopp (@lopp)&lt;/a&gt;
Libbitcoin developer @evoskuil on risk and security. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/eu7w1rNMPo&quot;&gt;https://t.co/eu7w1rNMPo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-07-26/i-just-got-robbed-bank-woman-finds-her-bofa-safe-deposit-box-has-vanished&quot;&gt;“I Was In Shock”: Woman Finds Her BofA Safe Deposit Box Has Vanished&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I just got robbed from the bank. They just took my stuff.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2018/08/15/cryptocurrency-investor-sues-att-for-224-million-over-loss-of-digita.html&quot;&gt;Cryptocurrency investor robbed via his cellphone account sues AT&amp;amp;T…&lt;/a&gt;
A U.S. investor files a $224 million lawsuit against AT&amp;amp;T accusing the telecommunications giant of negligence that allegedly caused the California resident to lose roughly $24 million in cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://diyhpl.us/wiki/transcripts/baltic-honeybadger/2018/extreme-opsec-for-the-modern-cypherpunk/&quot;&gt;Extreme opsec for the modern cypherpunk&lt;/a&gt; - Jameson Lopp (lopp) jameson@team.casa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=327767.0&quot;&gt;GHash.IO and double-spending against BetCoin Dice&lt;/a&gt;
GHash.IO and double-spending against BetCoin Dice&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nakamotoinstitute.org/trusted-third-parties/&quot;&gt;Trusted Third Parties are Security Holes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccn.com/op-ed-how-air-gap-technology-has-and-will-secure-our-cryptocurrency-assets&quot;&gt;Op-Ed: How Air Gap Technology Can Secure Our Cryptocurrency Assets&lt;/a&gt;
The truth is that anything connected to the internet can be hacked – even cryptocurrency wallets. However, hacking wasn’t always a problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lwsnbaker/status/1048060801880223744&quot;&gt;lawson baker : 88发 babafa (@lwsnbaker)&lt;/a&gt;
Holy crap. I knew hardware attacks were a very real risk. However, when it’s on every significant sever motherboard around (e.g. AWS, Apple, and NSA), you realize how screwed we are. Must read&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nopara73/status/1048268011856187399&quot;&gt;nopara73 (@nopara73)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;1/ My software recommendations to optimize your privacy. I just took control over the Wasabi website and originally I wanted to create a section there, but I am lazy, so this’ll only be a tweetstorm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/spencernoon/status/1051096114886270976&quot;&gt;Spencer Noon 🕛 (@spencernoon)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Online Security Pro Tips Mandatory —Delete phone number for 2FA —Google Authenticator or similar for 2FA Basic —Use a password manager —VPN for public WiFi Expert —Secret burner phone for mandatory text 2FA —Secure 2FA device (e.g. Yubikey) God Mode …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hackers-arise.com/post/2016/05/23/getting-started-with-kali-linux&quot;&gt;Getting Started with Kali Linux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/danheld/status/1090317203239460864&quot;&gt;Dan Hedl (@danheld)&lt;/a&gt;
Really excited to learn more about best in class private key management practices at the “Simple Cold Storage &amp;amp; Self-Custody” workshop with the pros: @anguschampion @ChristopherA @kanzure #SmartCustody&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nlw/status/1090716062222635010&quot;&gt;Nathaniel Whittemore (@nlw)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;What will it take to convince people that privacy is something that they have a right to?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/soonaorlater/status/1090704760963969024&quot;&gt;Soona - @soonaorlater&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;A popular metaphor: you dont close your house door bc youre doing something illegal you need to hide&lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;p&gt;Im a fan of the closed-door-in-your-home example. Its familiar. Its easy to understand. We practically live online so positioning the internet as a kinda 2nd abode isnt a stretch&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/wiz/status/1132538612317245441?s=12&quot;&gt;wiz (@wiz)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Unpopular Opinion: @signalapp sucks for both security and privacy because it uses phone numbers for identification and authentication. IMO the best chat app is @KeybaseIO which uses a cryptographic based identity system. They just need to add Bitcoin and remove the Shitc…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/wbm312/status/1140718569258287105?s=12&quot;&gt;Whitney Merrill (@wbm312)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I want to do a privacy &amp;amp; security training made up of tweets from the security &amp;amp; privacy community commenting on bad privacy &amp;amp; data security practices they see in real life. Anyone have good examples of old tweets? (e.g. this person was doing sensitive company stuff on a p…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=20404933&quot;&gt;Tell HN: I came up with an interesting way to do decentralized account recovery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Thought I’d share this with the HN community.Link to the Escrovery paper: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/pickhardt/escrovery/blob/master/escrovery...I&quot;&gt;https://github.com/pickhardt/escrovery/blob/master/escrovery…I&lt;/a&gt; came up with an interesting way to do totally decentralized account recovery. Why might this be useful? Suppose you have some account on …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SarahJamieLewis/status/1076267258064756738&quot;&gt;Sarah Jamie Lewis (@SarahJamieLewis)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There is something to be said about the idea that technology has evolved in such a way that corporate &amp;amp; government surveillance is easy, but personal quantification is difficult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nomeata/status/1097513606491660290&quot;&gt;Joachim Breitner (@nomeata)&lt;/a&gt;
Together with @nadiaheninger, just presented our work on biased nonces revealing secret keys in #bitcoin, #ethereum and #ripple at Financial Crypto #fc19. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/kMqQc7bJbL&quot;&gt;https://t.co/kMqQc7bJbL&lt;/a&gt; (photo by @zooko)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.schneier.com/&quot;&gt;Schneier on Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChristopherA/status/1086160862035902464&quot;&gt;Christopher Allen - @ChristopherA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;find these points a root concern of mine for many blockchain &amp;amp; identity projects as well. Bitcoin-core somehow avoids it, but I’m not sure how to bring some of that particular security culture elsewhere. It certainly can’t happen in #MVP &amp;amp; #Agile startup cultures. Alternatives?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChristopherA/status/1087216585499017216&quot;&gt;Christopher Allen (@ChristopherA)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;”arguments that quality bugs &amp;amp; security bugs ‘have equal value’, that security testing &amp;amp; QA are ‘the same thing’, that security testing should ‘just be performed by QA’ &amp;amp; that ‘there’s no specific skillset’ required to do security testing versus…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://hackingdistributed.com/2018/05/30/choose-your-own-security-disclosure-adventure&quot;&gt;Choose-Your-Own-Security-Disclosure-Adventure&lt;/a&gt;
In this Choose Your Own Adventure Game, you navigate the process of warning the world about an exploit you have uncovered in a large software project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@masonic_tweets/minimum-viable-security-32e61d10aee4&quot;&gt;Minimum Viable Security&lt;/a&gt;
The least you can do to frustrate would-be hackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.qubes-os.org/doc/certified-hardware&quot;&gt;Certified Hardware - qubes-os&lt;/a&gt;
Certified Hardware Important Information There is currently no specific hardware (e.g., specific laptop model) that the Qubes team recommends for individual users. However, we’re working hard to make a “reasonably secure laptop” a reality, and we look forward to sharing…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tor---onion-routing&quot;&gt;TOR - Onion Routing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/news/brave-advances-browser-privacy-with-tor-powered-tabs/&quot;&gt;Brave now protects your browsing activity with Tor-powered tabs&lt;/a&gt;
Onion routing is the way to go. It’s all about the layers of encryption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/notgrubles/status/1028319690937036805&quot;&gt;grubles (@notgrubles)&lt;/a&gt;
A Tor Hidden Service Mastodon instance, you say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/torproject/status/1035609722844585984&quot;&gt;The Tor Project (@torproject)&lt;/a&gt;
if you have basic command-line experience, you can become one of the thousands of relay operators powering the Tor network and protecting millions from tracking, surveillance, and censorship. Our guide can show you how: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/iBEVP1tUO6&quot;&gt;https://t.co/iBEVP1tUO6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whonix.org/wiki/Onion_Services&quot;&gt;Onion Services&lt;/a&gt;
Anonymously host any server with Whonix and Tor onion services&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/new-guide-running-tor-relay&quot;&gt;The New Guide to Running a Tor Relay | Tor Blog&lt;/a&gt;
Have you considered running a relay, but didn’t know where to start? You can become one of the many thousands of relay operators powering the Tor network, if you have some basic command-line experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whoishostingthis.com/blog/2014/11/17/who-funded-tor/&quot;&gt;Who Pays For Tor? (Hint: You Do)&lt;/a&gt;
Thanks to the Silk Road’s notoriety, Tor has quite the sinister reputation. The online black market is famous for facilitating the sale of anything from illegal drugs to murderers for hire. But there’s much more to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/neil_neilzone/status/1046726283047194624&quot;&gt;Neil Brown (@neil_neilzone)&lt;/a&gt;
I hadn’t seen @BriarApp until today - decentralised, p2p, e2e messaging via Tor. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/hSEJTSrslW&quot;&gt;https://t.co/hSEJTSrslW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/torproject/status/1073318560188022784&quot;&gt;The Tor Project (@torproject)&lt;/a&gt;
If Tor disappeared, what would happen? Not only would millions lose access, but the diverse ecosystem of privacy, security, and anti-censorship applications that rely on the Tor network would cease to function. An entire ecosystem relies on Tor. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/XVp1ajbFoz&quot;&gt;https://t.co/XVp1ajbFoz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kylesamani/status/1138469712180809728?s=12&quot;&gt;Kyle Samani (@KyleSamani)&lt;/a&gt;
Who are all of the teams working on economically incentived distributed VPN/Tor? Orchid, Mysterium, who else?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/aaronvanw/status/1138896611206160384?s=12&quot;&gt;Aaron van Wirdum (@AaronvanW)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“the fight against online drug sales is starting to resemble the war on drugs in the physical world: There are raids. Sites are taken down; a few people are arrested. And after a while the trade and markets pop up somewhere else.” Gee. (HT @chainalysis) &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/t5z&quot;&gt;https://t.co/t5z&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.is/KKr8d&quot;&gt;bible/buyer/about/before - DarkNetMarketsNoobs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=20485514&quot;&gt;Hackers breach FSB contractor, expose Tor deanonymization project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoinprimitives.libsyn.com/tor-project&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Primitives: S1:E8 TOR Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The goal of onion routing was to have a way to use the internet with as much privacy as possible, and the idea was to route traffic through multiple servers and encrypt it each step of the way. This is still a simple explanation for how Tor works today. &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.tor/&quot;&gt;https://support.tor&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/technology/audio/2012/apr/24/tech-weekly-podcast-tor-anonymity&quot;&gt;Aleks Krotoski talks to Andrew Lewman on Tor and anonymity online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aleks Krotoski talks to Andrew Lewman on Tor and anonymity online&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://theaverageguy.tv/2016/06/07/tor-and-anonymity-an-academic-introduction-to-the-dark-web-cf028/&quot;&gt;Tor and Anonymity: An Academic Introduction to the Dark Web – CF028&lt;/a&gt;
Listen Mobile: Cyber Frontiers is all about Exploring Cyber security, Big Data, and the Technologies Shaping the Future Through an Academic Perspective! Christian Johnson, a student at the University of Maryland will bring fresh and relevant topics to the show bas…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/michael-bazzell/the-complete-privacy-security-podcast&quot;&gt;The Privacy, Security, &amp;amp; OSINT Show&lt;/a&gt;
Listen to The Privacy, Security, &amp;amp; OSINT Show episodes free, on demand. Your weekly dose of privacy, digital security, and open source intelligence (OSINT) news and opinion. The easiest way to listen to podcasts on your iPhone, iPad, Android, PC, smart speaker – and even in…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bitcoin-threat-model&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Threat Model&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JWWeatherman&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/pfCQUAa.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_208 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_208---The-Bitcoin-Threat-Model-Part-1-e33vc0&quot;&gt;The Bitcoin Threat Model [Part 1]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_209 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_209---The-Bitcoin-Threat-Model-Part-2-e34ah8&quot;&gt;The Bitcoin Threat Model [Part 2]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_210 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_210---Human-Threat-Model-Part-1-e352ah&quot;&gt;Human Threat Model [Part 1]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_211 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_211---Human-Threat-Model-Part-2-e35ejd&quot;&gt;Human Threat Model [Part 2]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/The-Bitcoin-Threat-Model-e35f5r&quot;&gt;The Bitcoin Threat Model&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/security/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Security Info + Best Practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assorted Technical Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/privacy/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy and Bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/lightning/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin - Layer 2 - Lightning, Liquid and Beyond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-1/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Layer 1 - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/decentralization/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li class=&quot;text-right&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/feed/archive/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More ›&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;


  
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/info/security/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Assorted Articles, Tweets, and Short-Form</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/info/articles/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/info/2019-12-31-assorted-articles-tweets.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/info/2019-12-31-assorted-articles-tweets.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CryptoQuikRead_130 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_130---Media-Coverage-of-Bitcoin-is-Still-a-Total-Disaster-e2ndqf&quot;&gt;Media Coverage of Bitcoin is Still a Total Disaster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/xyZgkKE.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/66ZoGUAnY9s&quot;&gt;Baltic Honeybadger 2018 Bitcoin conference, Riga, day 1&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Timestamp:
35:48 - The Reserve Currency Fallacy by Eric Voskuil
1:05:34 - Trustlessness, Scalability, and Directions in Security Models by Matt Corallo
1:41:42 - 1 on 1: Current state of the market &amp;amp; institutional investors Leo Weiss with Tone Vays &amp;amp; Bruce Fenton
2:38:19 - The future of Bitcoin smart contracts by Max Keidun
3:02:50 - The Bitcoin Standard as a layered scaling solution by Saifedean Ammous (via Skype)
3:36:10 - Beyond Bitcoin: Decentralized collaboration by Yurii Rashkovskii 
4:06:30 - 1 on 1: The future of Bitcoin wallets with Pavol Rusnak &amp;amp; Lawrence Nahum, moderated by Giacomo Zucco
5:48:10 - Extreme OPSEC for the Modern Cypherpunk by Jameson Lopp
6:24:20 - 1 on 1: Bitcoin payment processing and merchants with Sergej Kotliar &amp;amp; Alena Vranova, moderated by Vortex
6:55:01 - 1 on 1: Present and future tech challenges in Bitcoin with Peter Todd &amp;amp; Adam Back, moderated by Pierre Roberge
7:48:45 - The Future of Lightning by Elizabeth Stark
8:24:10 - 1 on 1: Investing in bitcoin businesses with Nic Carter &amp;amp; Florian Maier, moderated by Matthew Mežinskis
8:52:10 - Closing panel with Elizabeth Stark, Peter Todd, Jameson Lopp, Eric Voskuil, Alex Petrov, moderated by Roman Snitko&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theblockcrypto.com/2018/11/01/mapping-out-bitcoins-supply-chain/&quot;&gt;Mapping out bitcoin’s supply chain - The Block&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The Block complements our writings and analyses with charts, graphs, and maps is to give our readers a comprehensive look at the complex crypto ecosystem. Even the veteran Bitcoiner can get lost in the twist and turns that is the bitcoin labyrinth. Here, we take a high-level…
&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/1XOFJBx.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@timevalueofbtc/the-business-of-bitcoin-cold-storage-148fba7f1255&quot;&gt;The Business of Bitcoin Cold Storage – Nik Bhatia&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is digital gold, and this continues to be its most appropriate and concise metaphor. I recently discussed some parallels between…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pierre_rochard/status/988403000682139649&quot;&gt;Pierre Rochard [⚡️] (@pierre_rochard)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Why I’m focused on Bitcoin: • Schelling point consensus • p2p network governance with full nodes • proof-of-work secure timestamping • Lindy effect / first mover advantage • fixed issuance schedule • prudent engineering culture • promising research: lightni…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/PKeAZi4YKb0&quot;&gt;Bitcoin or Shitcoin? (highlights from our Spectator debate)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;BitMEX’s recent live event with The Spectator (“Who’s afraid of Bitcoin?”) was an exclusive affair, with fewer than 200 people in the theatre. All the sessio…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TheLTBNetwork/status/1062773855289270272&quot;&gt;The LTB Network [Jan/3➞₿ 🔑∎] (@TheLTBNetwork)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Check out the latest episode of @TheCryptoShow featuring @ProfFaustus and @DanielKrawisz - this time discussing thoughts on the #fork, the origins of #bitcoin and #LightningNetwork. https://t.co/TpRGZ4MPMM&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@festina_lente_2/why-bitcoin-is-not-a-startup-23c6b772f360&quot;&gt;Why Bitcoin Is Not a Startup – The Bitcoin Observer – Part II — MoE As a Unique Type of Economic Good&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1200/1*j_dLZGVM7rV8wsJRronzyA.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AaronvanW/status/1079801323967709185&quot;&gt;Aaron van Wirdum (@AaronvanW)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Blockchain Analysis Is About to Get Harder as P2EP Enters Testing Phase. https://t.co/EtrlMxpW8N Happy new year!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Dv3BAhNV4AEzTss.jpg:large&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/coinmonks/why-bitcoin-has-value-by-a-millennial-4ac7eff4ee7d&quot;&gt;Why Bitcoin Has Value by a Millennial – Coinmonks&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Many arguments against Bitcoin can be summed up as, “But it has no intrinsic value!” But what is value, even? The world is currently in a…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@lopp/bitcoin-by-the-numbers-2018-recap-68a91789d804&quot;&gt;Bitcoin By the Numbers: 2018 Recap – Jameson Lopp&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’ve always been fascinated with the raw numbers relating to the operational status and growth of Bitcoin, especially as we ride the…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/btc/comments/8ps659/history_lesson_in_2013_peter_todd_was_paid_off_by/&quot;&gt;r/btc - History lesson: In 2013, Peter Todd was paid off by a gove…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/crossphd/status/1080196216011534336&quot;&gt;Christopher Ross (@crossphd)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin and the Promise of Independent Property Rights by @hasufl https://t.co/W53PwjpNdE&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/casa/the-evolution-of-bitcoin-key-management-c2fd29ba35d6&quot;&gt;The Evolution of Bitcoin Key Management&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Let’s revisit important milestones in how we experienced Bitcoin HODLing over the past 10 years, and what we can expect from 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;In this post, I’m not talking about custodial “vaults” — exchanges and wallets that hold crypto on the customer’s behalf — nor all the security faux-pas and breaches that happened in custody. This is merely my appreciation for the development of the sovereign Bitcoiner.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/GettyImages-700711715.jpg?w=599&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/seth586/status/1111675972728832001&quot;&gt;Seth586😈guides [BIP157+FULL NODE]⚡ (@seth586)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I just published Neutrino can be dangerous, so lets grow Bitcoin’s immunity with a BIP/BOLT https://t.co/I0IBwtR8x7&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/evoskuil/status/1116242776092336133?s=12&quot;&gt;Eric Voskuil (@evoskuil)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Substitution Principle” is the 62nd topic in the series on understanding #bitcoin: https://t.co/f00mq70Edp&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://kauri.io/article/ef32ddae59094e8b99c92131b9148200&quot;&gt;Visualizing Bitcoin Transactions in 3D and Virtual Reality&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Abstract Bitcoin transactions form a graph that can be visualized in 3D and Virtual Reality (VR). This article explores how you can see these visualizations. The image below shows some of the network of transactions linked to the bitcoin pizza transaction . The red cubes are …&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/csuwildcat/status/1121765393419235333?s=12&quot;&gt;Daniel Ƀ (@csuwildcat)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Someone asked about Bitcoin/cryptocurrency volatility last night at an event, suggesting it can’t be good at what it’s supposed to do unless it’s as stable as USD - my response: “It operates as the most advanced DPKI layer we’ve ever seen, whether the price is $1 or $1 mil…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ericturnr/status/1122589759644360706?s=12&quot;&gt;Eric Turner (@ericturnr)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Started putting together some research on “bitcoin banks” inspired by @nic__carter. So far I am interested but not sold on the idea. What sources am I missing? https://t.co/6QaEakpLZg&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/imacallyoujawdy/status/1130852270470385665?s=12&quot;&gt;Permabull Niño (@ImacallyouJawdy)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;As part 1 of a 4 part series that @MustStopMurad and myself are teaming up for, we’re excited to explore Bitcoin with you from an accounting point of view, via: https://t.co/kBrK3NYqX5&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_067 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_067---Giacomo-Zuccos-Epic-Twitter-Thread-e2ndsi&quot;&gt;Giacomo Zucco’s Epic Twitter Thread&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://threadreaderapp.com/thread/991438132812943369.html&quot;&gt;threadreaderapp.com/thread/991438132812943369.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;takes&quot;&gt;Takes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ragnarly/status/1129951605787226112?s=12&quot;&gt;Ragnar Lifthrasir 🏴 (@Ragnarly)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;@brian_trollz @peterktodd Bitcoin is a place where we can all learn, make mistakes, and sometimes be assholes, but be quickly forgiven. Unless you don’t admit your mistakes anddouble down on them. I think Bitcoin is a relatively benign, forgiving place. But I grew up dif…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChristopherA/status/1088999047367553025&quot;&gt;Christopher Allen (@ChristopherA)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The view amongst most bitcoin people I know is not that they don’t care about privacy or fungibility — they care very very much…But it’s one that cannot fail, or it’s one that we better not cause to fail. And that takes precedence over everything else.”— A…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/btcblackcab/status/1088975839595773953&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Black Cab (@btcblackcab)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’m fed up with being judged as unreasonable for supporting bitcoin. I’m interested in bitcoin. No one says to an ethereum supporter “why don’t you give credence to dentacoin or doge or whatever”. I back bitcoin and I back people that back bitcoin. https://t.co/…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/dksf/status/1039955893675155456&quot;&gt;David 🖍 @dksf&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;1/ Censorship Resistant Non-Sovereign Monetary Store Of Value is a simple Bitcoin utility which doesn’t require that I find the other participants to transact with to get utility (though I must believe they exist). It’s functionally similar to a single-player mode for Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/KyleSamani/status/1042784168487387137&quot;&gt;Kyle Samani (@KyleSamani)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;0/ Bitcoin is by definition a pyramid scheme / multi-level marketing scheme&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;To be fair, it’s the most “fair” and egalitarian pyramid scheme ever devised, but it is none the less a pyramid scheme&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jaybny/status/1004929885528178689&quot;&gt;Jay 4.669 [ #NOhalfX ]&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Fundamental theory of Bitcoin: Distributed consensus can be reached on the condition, 
1) nodes continuously and indpendently derived the same random variables 
2) outcome is independently verifiable
3) real world effort implicitly tied to digital signatures&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SatoshiLite/status/1048468911929274368&quot;&gt;Charlie Lee [LTC⚡] (@SatoshiLite)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;1/ On-chain Bitcoin and Litecoin payments are not peer-to-peer. Payments are sent from sender to miners, who record it on a distributed ledger. The recipient receives the payment when it’s recorded. BUT, this is facilitated by a p2p network where transactions are broadcast…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;articles&quot;&gt;Articles&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/misir_mahmudov/status/1039561835240939524&quot;&gt;Misir Mahmudov (@misir_mahmudov)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mandatory Bitcoin articles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Bullish Case for Bitcoin @real_vijay&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Crash Course in Bitcoin Pol. Economy @NakamotoInst&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Money, blockchains &amp;amp; social scalability @NickSzabo4&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;An Inst. Investor’s Take on Cryptoassets @jlppfeffer&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Cryptocurrencies are money, not equity @BMB…
&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Dm1Azy4V4AAdaDw.png:large&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.patreon.com/posts/its-time-to-stop-14695811&quot;&gt;Its time to stop ‘pretending’. You don’t own Bitcoin.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Official Post from Chris DeRose: You don’t own Bitcoin. There, someone had to say it. Might as well be me. Owning Bitcoin was a great meme. Had an awesome run. But you don’t own it, and never did. Sound delusional? Nope. By the end of this article, you will probably agree. W…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/blockchain-bullies-truth-trolling-bitcoin-uncensoreds-big-short/&quot;&gt;Blockchain ‘Bullies’: Truth, Trolls and Bitcoin Uncensored&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Bailey Reutzel speaks to the controversial pair behind Bitcoin Uncensored and tries to separate their truths from their blockchain industry trolling.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.picks.co/bitcoins-distribution-was-fair-e2ef7bbbc892&quot;&gt;Bitcoin’s Distribution Was Fair – Picks &amp;amp; Shovels Debunking FUD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/op-ed-there-grain-truth-every-joke/&quot;&gt;Op Ed: There Is a Satoshi of Truth in Every Joke&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://btcmag.portal.btcm.ag/wp-content/uploads/sites/5/2019/06/gp-truth-in-joke.width-800-722x401.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@laurentmt/the-yin-and-yang-of-bitcoin-bf056f3fd58c&quot;&gt;The Yin and Yang of Bitcoin – LaurentMT – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Countless words count less than the silent balance between yin and yang” - Laotzi&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@laurentmt/cliffhangers-cb87ed47124e&quot;&gt;Cliffhangers – LaurentMT – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Be like the cliff against which the waves continually break; but it stands firm and tames the fury of the water around it.” — Marcus…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hackernoon.com/why-isnt-bitcoin-banned-everywhere-32a2caec90&quot;&gt;Why isn’t Bitcoin banned everywhere? – Hacker Noon&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Bitcoin was supposed to be the enemy of governments. And yet most countries have ushered it through the front door. What’s the explanation?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@2W/the-exact-definition-of-blockchain-225b96a5e2b9&quot;&gt;The Exact Definition of ‘Blockchain’ – Tim Pastoor&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1200/1*545rq_Hfo9G2vAupqDAKfQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/danheld/status/1055499653930672129&quot;&gt;Dan Hedl (@danheld)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;1/ Bitcoin’s origin is akin to planting a tree. It wasn’t just Satoshi’s selection of the species (code), but the season (timing), soil (distribution), and gardening (community) that were essential to its success Part 1: Species https://t.co/mfgMaDx70Z Thread 👇&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cryptoquickreads&quot;&gt;CryptoQuickReads&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_014 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_014---Bulletproofs--Faster-Rangeproofs--and-Much-More-e2ndue&quot;&gt;Bulletproofs, Faster Rangeproofs, and Much More&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_045 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_045---Why-Schnorr-Signatures-will-Solve-2-of-Bitcoins-Biggest-Problems-e2ndt9&quot;&gt;Why Schnorr Signatures will Solve 2 of Bitcoin’s Biggest Problems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_053 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_053---Pieter-Wuille-Chapioning-Bitcoin-Development-e2ndt0&quot;&gt;Pieter Wuille Chapioning Bitcoin Development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_114 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_114---Schnorr-Poised-to-Become-Bitcoins-Biggest-Change-Since-SegWit-e2ndr1&quot;&gt;Schnorr Poised to Become Bitcoin’s Biggest Change Since SegWit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuickRead_035 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuickRead_035---The-Digital-Age-of-Securities-e2ndtl&quot;&gt;The Digital Age of Securities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_103 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_103---Crypto-Commons-e2ndre&quot;&gt;Crypto Commons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_173 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_173---Reimagining-Trusted-Intermediaries-e2ndov&quot;&gt;Reimagining Trusted Intermediaries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoChat_003 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoChat_003---Nik-Bhatia-on-The-Future-of-Bitcoin-Financial-Markets-e2ndqv&quot;&gt;Nik Bhatia on The Future of Bitcoin Financial Markets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/info/articles/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Bitcoin Swag - Clothing and Accessories</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/swag/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/social/2019-12-30-swag.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/social/2019-12-30-swag.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LayerOneBTC&quot;&gt;LayerOneBTC.com (@LayerOneBTC)&lt;/a&gt;
Bitcoin apparel &amp;amp; merch by @nckbtc — Designs emphasize characteristics essential to bitcoin’s core principles. Shirts, hats, hoodies &amp;amp; more&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.redbubble.com/people/curbapparel/works/26597494-nerd-money-bitcoin-crypto-blockchain-btc?p=classic-tee&quot;&gt;‘Nerd Money- Bitcoin Crypto Blockchain BTC’ Classic T-Shirt by cur…&lt;/a&gt;
Nerd Money – Bitcoin Crypto Blockchain • Also buy this artwork on apparel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ih1.redbubble.net/image.377167858.7494/ra,classic_tee,x2100,5e504c:7bf03840f4,front-c,355,131,750,1000-bg,f8f8f8.lite-1u1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://ih1.redbubble.net/image.377167858.7494/ra,classic_tee,x2100,5e504c:7bf03840f4,front-c,355,131,750,1000-bg,f8f8f8.lite-1u1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/NeerajKA/status/1035327501650853893&quot;&gt;Neeraj K. Agrawal (@NeerajKA)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;ok this is pretty clever (h/t @kateclarktweets) &lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Dl44vjZU4AIH0TL?format=jpg&amp;amp;name=small&quot; alt=&quot;https://t.co/H6bUnTO8VI&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/BITCOINTELPRO&quot;&gt;BITCOINTELPRO (@BITCOINTELPRO)&lt;/a&gt;
Crypto Clothing for Bitcoiners, by Bitcoiners&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptophones.myshopify.com/&quot;&gt;Bullish Crypto&lt;/a&gt;
Clothing that’s as bullish as you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cryptoartlab.com/postershop/&quot;&gt;Crypto Art Lab - Original Posters with Crypto Anarchy Topics&lt;/a&gt;
Hand screen printed posters, limited series, numbered and signed by author. Original artwork, worldwide shipping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lynxartcollection.com/&quot;&gt;Lynx Art Collection&lt;/a&gt;
Artwork engineered to generate emotion. Limited art prints, canvases, metal panels, and collectibles from crypto such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and Monero, along with artwork from Space, Science, Travel, &amp;amp; History. We’ve been sparking conversations since 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/swag/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Art and Memes</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/memes-art/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/social/2019-12-30-memes-art.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/social/2019-12-30-memes-art.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://noded.org/podcast/noded-0260-with-bitcoin-sign-guy/&quot;&gt;Noded 0.26.0 with Bitcoin Sign Guy&lt;/a&gt;
Michael Goldstein and Pierre Rochard talk with Bitcoin Sign Guy about Bitcoin memetics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fineartamerica.com/art/bitcoin&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Art | Fine Art America&lt;/a&gt;
Shop for bitcoin art from the world’s greatest living artists. All bitcoin artwork ships within 48 hours and includes a 30-day money-back guarantee. Choose your favorite bitcoin designs and purchase them as wall art, home decor, phone cases, tote bags, and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccn.com/uk-art-gallery-becomes-the-first-to-accept-bitcoin-to-art-buyers/&quot;&gt;UK Art Gallery becomes the First to Accept Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;
A Mayfair art gallery has become the first in the UK to accept six digital currencies including bitcoin, ethereum and ethereum classic to art buyers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/luchopoletti/status/1167246333713014784?s=12&quot;&gt;Lucho (@LuchoPoletti)&lt;/a&gt;
Designing #Bitcoin wallets with public addresses. Here’s one I made for myself. Any tips sent here will fund the creation #BitcoinArt &amp;amp; #Propaganda&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/cryptocurrencymemes/comments/cx7ux8/i_cant_believe_its_not_bitcoin/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&quot;&gt;r/cryptocurrencymemes - I can’t believe it’s not Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@HashedEntropy/what-hath-satoshi-wrought-f7687b631d42&quot;&gt;What Hath Satoshi Wrought&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t3cqUYqmW9M&quot;&gt;“Blockchain and Morty” - THE SHILLING (Full Episode)&lt;/a&gt;
I really hope you all enjoy this. This is my first full episode, and it’s an exploration of “Crypto Tribalism” and some of the toxic attitudes I’ve come acro…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Beastlyorion/status/1042922583539081216&quot;&gt;Parabolic Beastlorion (@Beastlyorion)&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Dnk0j-pUwAALJ8u?format=jpg&amp;amp;name=small&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y3dqhixzGVo&quot;&gt;Mining Bitcoin with pencil and paper&lt;/a&gt;
Bitcoins are mined using a cryptographic algorithm called SHA-256. This algorithm is simple enough to be done with pencil and paper, as I show in this video….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/495741202306433024/5t93zh8c19p11.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/495741202306433024/5t93zh8c19p11.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/496139334282510336/Dn3yzvYXcAISuja.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/496139334282510336/Dn3yzvYXcAISuja.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Dnxk6CdWsAIQ8Dj.jpg:large&quot; alt=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Dnxk6CdWsAIQ8Dj.jpg:large&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChartsBtc/status/1044982364093308930&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Charts (no TA) (@ChartsBtc)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin price on this date (Sept. 26th) #Bitcoin $BTC #BitcoinCharts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://steemkr.com/bitshares/@barrydutton/meme-ing-the-blockchain-or-e-23-or-the-b-s-man-the-b-s-bitshares-too-from-your-blogger-barry&quot;&gt;Meme’ing the Blockchain: | E.23 | The B’s Man, the B’s…..Bit…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We are all early adopters here, if you are even close to reading this today. I say this OFTEN to remind people.… by barrydutton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://steemitimages.com/DQmRapJdHim4t271eX2wsvoxZCErqTZF6p8ns2Fyxtmz4T2/image.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://steemitimages.com/DQmRapJdHim4t271eX2wsvoxZCErqTZF6p8ns2Fyxtmz4T2/image.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CryptoBrekkie/status/1053662330850951168&quot;&gt;Spooky Brekkie von Bitcoin [GIVING AWAY LÖLZ] (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/992075328192311296/pu/img/1mQc6C8J_n1Uf8GP.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/992075328192311296/pu/img/1mQc6C8J_n1Uf8GP.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1054520588734058496&quot;&gt;Elon Musk (@elonmusk)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/DqJo4XUU8AAVUcl?format=jpg&amp;amp;name=900x900&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ZachSmolinski/status/1048277539033153538&quot;&gt;Zach Smolinski (@ZachSmolinski)&lt;/a&gt;
Blockchain is the first data structure to successfully become a lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/508680271026192384/DMfIgdoVQAEQHmb.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/508680271026192384/DMfIgdoVQAEQHmb.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/508705116321349652/DpHhe7rU8AAPn3b.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/508705116321349652/DpHhe7rU8AAPn3b.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pinguino/status/1051297608910553088&quot;&gt;Pinguino 🎃 (@pinguino)&lt;/a&gt;
24 hour #bitcoin comic - Page one&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/KanyeOnSecurity/status/1050473358666674176&quot;&gt;InfoSec Kanye West (@KanyeOnSecurity)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RNR_0/status/1052686873561157632&quot;&gt;[ Romano ] (@RNR_0)&lt;/a&gt;
The Onion’s guide to Blockchain &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/xqkXldY3NM&quot;&gt;https://t.co/xqkXldY3NM&lt;/a&gt; (tweet stolen from @jebus911 but I included a screenshot because I know you guys are lazy)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/509358472064663552/image0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/509358472064663552/image0.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/uwYpMm6KZx&quot;&gt;https://t.co/uwYpMm6KZx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/uwYpMm6KZx&quot;&gt;Blockchain and Morty! - YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://yetanotherico.com/&quot;&gt;http://yetanotherico.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/516431275741937671/Dq0nyIDW4AEUcc4.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/516431275741937671/Dq0nyIDW4AEUcc4.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/516431793549737994/Dq1wK3CWsAAd0Ui.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/516431793549737994/Dq1wK3CWsAAd0Ui.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL2hao8YIqjZOwU7jGVsb3_ypqI8gnxVQY&quot;&gt;Blockchain and Morty! - YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/t3cqUYqmW9M/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEWCKgBEF5IWvKriqkDCQgBFQAAiEIYAQ==&amp;amp;rs=AOn4CLA41DdeK9vt87FekbiyD1ihN7HP3g&quot; alt=&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/t3cqUYqmW9M/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEWCKgBEF5IWvKriqkDCQgBFQAAiEIYAQ==&amp;amp;rs=AOn4CLA41DdeK9vt87FekbiyD1ihN7HP3g&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCSuHzQ3GrHSzoBbwrIq3LLA&quot;&gt;Naomi Brockwell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qQ7jODfM4m0&amp;amp;list=PLt3zZ-N423gVWo682EZzhrgAJYVS1yYde&quot;&gt;Crypto Wonderland (acoustic) - Steemit Open Mic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Thrilled to get an honorable mention in Steemit Open Mic Week 115! Here’s my entry, Crypto Wonderland! It’s part of my weekly song challenge, this week’s son…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CryptoBrekkie&quot;&gt;Brekkie von Bitcoin ✌🏻❤️🚀 [GIVING AWAY LÖLZ] (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;
Dedicated to @ProfFaustus #BCash
&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/1063260749974319105/pu/img/4M_dGE2M_ilKGfu9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/1063260749974319105/pu/img/4M_dGE2M_ilKGfu9.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CryptoBrekkie/status/1064548151556620288&quot;&gt;Brekkie von Bitcoin ✌🏻❤️🚀 [GIVING AWAY LÖLZ] (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;@cryptinfominer @CRYPTOK1RK No worries. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/uwYpMm6KZx&quot;&gt;https://t.co/uwYpMm6KZx&lt;/a&gt; will take you to most of them. YouTube has blocked some, so the rest are available on @BitTubeApp &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/6W3VtORpnv&quot;&gt;https://t.co/6W3VtORpnv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RichardHeartWin/status/1066893092954013696&quot;&gt;Richard Heart [BitcoinHEX] (@RichardHeartWin)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/1066892965388402691/pu/img/lcgCXcEPyhr6tcyn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/1066892965388402691/pu/img/lcgCXcEPyhr6tcyn.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://designmodo.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/11-Cryptocurrency-by-Symbolon.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://designmodo.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/11-Cryptocurrency-by-Symbolon.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/526310339269099541/unknown.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/526310339269099541/unknown.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/avatars/220181860267851776/a_7931f5c980464827eadf1deed3016dad.gif&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/avatars/220181860267851776/a_7931f5c980464827eadf1deed3016dad.gif&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/i/status/1073192310408663044&quot;&gt;mocho17™ (@cryptomocho)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;literal found some cash that got losted 1 week ago now im filling like #crypto &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/8DWKEIp3ac&quot;&gt;https://t.co/8DWKEIp3ac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/naomibrockwell/status/1074720885104394241&quot;&gt;Naomi Brockwell (@naomibrockwell)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Walking in a crypto wonderland :) Watch the first single from Brekkie and Brockers’ Christmas Album! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/SqZHmeJ3Ii&quot;&gt;https://t.co/SqZHmeJ3Ii&lt;/a&gt; Watch the whole album on loop through our @BitBacker_io page: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/Y8dI6EADGp&quot;&gt;https://t.co/Y8dI6EADGp&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/T263M0zqfb&quot;&gt;https://t.co/T263M0zqfb&lt;/a&gt; @CryptoBrekkie&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/537522310509494272/DuZFsQdWkAAQhQJ.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/537522310509494272/DuZFsQdWkAAQhQJ.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media0.giphy.com/media/1wqK5FxWrxh2egQr0b/giphy_s.gif?cid=73b8f7b15c96f8e8735a696f411ddaa9&quot; alt=&quot;https://media0.giphy.com/media/1wqK5FxWrxh2egQr0b/giphy_s.gif?cid=73b8f7b15c96f8e8735a696f411ddaa9&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media1.giphy.com/media/182RoBRPuNyMKH8Rsx/giphy_s.gif?cid=73b8f7b15c96f9554a545477364f1de4&quot; alt=&quot;https://media1.giphy.com/media/182RoBRPuNyMKH8Rsx/giphy_s.gif?cid=73b8f7b15c96f9554a545477364f1de4&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/UaSoZf9.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/UaSoZf9.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cryptobrekkie/status/1114346867985244161?s=12&quot;&gt;Brekkie von Bitcoin🍯🦡⚡️ [GIVING AWAY LÖLZ] (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Doesn’t look like much, but I’m gonna shape &amp;amp; polish this brick into something magical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/proofofsteve/status/1119885149015904256?s=12&quot;&gt;Steve ₿ (@ProofOfSteve)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep accumulating during the bear markets &amp;amp; upgrading your level of sea life. Remember you have to start as a ‘Plankton’ before you become a ‘Blue Whale’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep believing #Bitcoin will be the new financial paradigm. Your patience will be rewarded beyond your wildest ima…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/572554070397550592/image.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/572554070397550592/image.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/575566426795147274/word-image-43-150x150.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/575566426795147274/word-image-43-150x150.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;retro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/575566481329356801/deepweb-150x150.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/575566481329356801/deepweb-150x150.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lowstrife/status/1131222240626860033?s=12&quot;&gt;lowstrife (@lowstrife)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;@mBTCPizpie @Crypto_Bitlord yo dwang, I heard you like paid groups, so I took your paid group leader and paid him to start another paid group so that you can pay your group while also paying your group leader&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mihailobjelic/status/1131923310483267590?s=12&quot;&gt;Mihailo Bjelic (@MihailoBjelic)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I am:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;single&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;in a relationship&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;married&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;trying to decode yet another zero knowledge whitepaper&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cryptobrekkie/status/1132795369123864576?s=12&quot;&gt;₿rekkie von ₿itcoin ⚡️ (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My shirt is more decentralized than&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cryptobrekkie/status/1132839156583784448?s=12&quot;&gt;₿rekkie von ₿itcoin ⚡️ (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;
Seems appropriate..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ep 5 “The Bear Market’s F$cking Over!”
&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/984274643077890049/pu/img/xmlwglD90hb1htGA.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/984274643077890049/pu/img/xmlwglD90hb1htGA.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bitcoindayla/status/1132011049719349250?s=12&quot;&gt;Bitcoinday (@BitcoindayLa)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muchas gracias a @franamati por su introducción a #bitcoin durante el #Bitcoinday_UY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cryptobrekkie/status/1133513087720468480?s=12&quot;&gt;₿rekkie von ₿itcoin ⚡️ (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cinemagraphs are the best. Fiat is the worst. #BuyBitcoin &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/aVa3Ff2HOd&quot;&gt;https://t.co/aVa3Ff2HOd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kimdhamilton/status/1134004060636368896?s=12&quot;&gt;Kim Hamilton Duffy (@kimdhamilton)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Me on permissioned blockchains &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/hHQLWfoFuR&quot;&gt;https://t.co/hHQLWfoFuR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/excellion/status/1136020651586854914?s=12&quot;&gt;Samson Mow (@Excellion)&lt;/a&gt; - I worked hard for this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cryptobrekkie/status/1136522482611961857?s=12&quot;&gt;₿rekkie von ₿itcoin ⚡️ (@CryptoBrekkie)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Add Bitcoin emoji artist to my profile&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/589656507168063519/BTC_9000.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/589656507168063519/BTC_9000.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/BitmexRekt/status/1140121688035790848&quot;&gt;REKT (@BitmexRekt)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Liquidated short on XBTUSD: Buy 10,000,000 @ 9102&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Cyberpunk/comments/c2m4zn/voodoo_boys_by_josan_gonzales/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&quot;&gt;r/Cyberpunk - Voodoo Boys by Josan Gonzales&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;124 votes and 2 comments so far on Reddit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ln4vynbggd531.jpg?auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9b8c568e2027a3b72ed09db1d85b81c59103536b&quot; alt=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ln4vynbggd531.jpg?auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9b8c568e2027a3b72ed09db1d85b81c59103536b&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/591077226443833360/4u4iqehqmb531.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/486744084761935872/591077226443833360/4u4iqehqmb531.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/talkshopcrypto/status/1141435976172154882?s=12&quot;&gt;TalkShopCrypto (@TalkShopCrypto)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Video speaks for itself lol Title: “Bitcoin doesnt care about your TA” Author is decentralife_ Found on Reddit #crypto #bitcoin #bitcoinmeme #cryptomeme #cryptomemes #funnymemes #funny #cryptomarket #TA #cryptodaily #dailynews #cryptonews #cryptocurrencies #eth #x…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/1141435898095198208/pu/img/T1Xqwjs-1oC923DT.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/ext_tw_video_thumb/1141435898095198208/pu/img/T1Xqwjs-1oC923DT.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bneiluj/status/1141626887871053824?s=12&quot;&gt;🚀🤺Julien Bouteloup - giver of Libra 😏 (@bneiluj)&lt;/a&gt; - End of an Era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cryptoeuclid/status/1142257309101580289?s=12&quot;&gt;Crypto Euclid (@CryptoEuclid)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Wut we gonna do at 11K guys? &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/lPdEMbZvvw&quot;&gt;https://t.co/lPdEMbZvvw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/_scottdarby/status/1148185267083370497&quot;&gt;sᴄᴏᴛᴛ ᴅᴀʀʙʏ (@_scottdarby)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project I’ve been building for over a year is finally live! A realtime 3D Blockchain Explorer that runs in the browser: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/IOWZgRn2ok&quot;&gt;https://t.co/IOWZgRn2ok&lt;/a&gt; Visit any block in Bitcoin’s history + hear a unique soundscape generated from the block data. #webgl #threejs #javascript #d…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://symphony.iohk.io/en/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Blockchain Visualised in 3D&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=20410049&quot;&gt;news.ycombinator.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This looks like something from Tron, trippy. The height of the block is the amount of BTC, there are some huge (thousands of BTC) transactions happening. On a semi related note, I built a 3D visualization (globe) to see where these blocks are geographically mined. &lt;a href=&quot;https://co/&quot;&gt;https://co&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/whiterabbitbtc/status/1183370538284146690?s=12&quot;&gt;WhiteRabbit (@WhiteRabbitBTC)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Hall of Shame&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/memes-art/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Bitcoin Media: Blogs, Podcasts, Video Channels, etc</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/info/audio-video/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/info/2019-12-30-audio-video.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/info/2019-12-30-audio-video.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;podcasts&quot;&gt;Podcasts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sourcecrypto.pub/blog/thecryptoconomy-podcast-deep-dive/&quot;&gt;The Cryptoconomy Podcast - Guy Swann&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Audio for Hundreds of Essential Bitcoin Articles. @TheCryptoconomy - Guy Swan….. These Podcasts are essential. So I made an index of them, organized by topic.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jupiterbroadcasting.com/show/planb/&quot;&gt;Jupiter Broadcasting - Plan B&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointechtalk.com/&quot;&gt;bitcointechtalk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-world-crypto-network-podcast/id825708806&quot;&gt;The World Crypto Network&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The World Crypto Network is an independent media organization that keeps you up to date with the latest news on Bitcoin and cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/noded-bitcoin-podcast&quot;&gt;Noded Bitcoin Podcast&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/noded-bitcoin-podcast/noded-0270-with-vortex&quot;&gt;Noded Bitcoin Podcast&lt;/a&gt; - Noded 0.27.0 with Vortex&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoincopodcast.com/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin &amp;amp; Co. - Introducing the philosophy, ideas and people behind Bitcoin.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinundco.com/en/andreas-antonopoulos-future/&quot;&gt;Andreas M. Antonopoulos on Bitcoin, privacy, human rights and the …&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Andreas M. Antonopoulos is one of the rare bitcoin and open blockchain experts who approaches the subject from an educational, political, cultural, and human perspective - not only discussing the technology in investment terms. We discuss Bitcoin in the context of human righ…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://letstalkbitcoin.com/&quot;&gt;Home | Lets Talk Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The LTB Network provides a tokenized platform for podcasts, articles, and forums about the ideas, people, and projects building the new digital economy and the future of money.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stephanlivera.com/&quot;&gt;Stephan Livera Podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://talesfromthecrypt.libsyn.com/&quot;&gt;Tales from the Crypt: A Bitcoin Podcast&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Tales from the Crypt is a podcast hosted by Marty Bent about Bitcoin. Join Marty, Editor in Chief of “the best newsletter in crypto”, as he sits down to discuss Bitcoin with interesting people. Support this podcast: &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/tales-from-the-crypt/support&quot;&gt;https://anchor.fm/tales-from-the-crypt/support&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blockworksgroup.io/untold-stories-podcast&quot;&gt;Untold Stories Podcast with Charlie Shrem&lt;/a&gt;
On Untold Stories, host Charlie Shrem dives deep into the lives and personal histories of some of crypto’s most influential leaders&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whatbitcoindid.com/&quot;&gt;What Bitcoin Did - Bitcoin Podcast, Interviews and Resources&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Listen to Interviews with leaders in Bitcoin and Cryptocurrencies with The What Bitcoin Did Podcast.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://citizenbitcoin.world/episodes&quot;&gt;Episodes | Citizen Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Podcasting my journey learning bitcoin hoping it makes yours a bit easier.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitcoin.kn/&quot;&gt;The Bitcoin Knowledge Podcast&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;To help you better understand Bitcoin the top people in the Bitcoin industry are interviewed by Trace Mayer for the Bitcoin Knowledge Podcast.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;video&quot;&gt;Video&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/Y-w7SnQWwVA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL05dEp7goGNiKWYdiE4nurEPFMmF9XpzF&quot;&gt;BitcoinExplainers.com Learn About Bitcoin on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The best way to learn about bitcoin is to actually use it. Perhaps the second best way is to watch some introductory videos. Please keep in mind the dates th…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHFL9uTsDbOuBtkhfabU38w&quot;&gt;Crypto Cast Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL05dEp7goGNiKWYdiE4nurEPFMmF9XpzF&quot;&gt;BitcoinExplainers.com Learn About Bitcoin on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/aantonop&quot;&gt;@aanontop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCt-Po2gFQxiUngwJXh6s04w/videos&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Wednesday&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“Bitcoin Wednesday: The Monthly Conference on Digital Currency in The Netherlands”&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/MITBitcoinClub/videos&quot;&gt;MIT Bitcoin Club&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/IamSatoshiNakamoto/videos&quot;&gt;IamSatoshi — In Decentralization We trust&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;we get to learn about the origin and ethics of Bitcoin’s developers, and explore their wide spectrum of professions, beliefs and social representation. We will try to uncover how they see Bitcoin, the message.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/MScDigitalCurrency/videos&quot;&gt;MSc in Digital Currency -  University of Nicosia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCgo7FCCPuylVk4luP3JAgVw/videos&quot;&gt;Congressional Research Institute&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQ9eXM9P9-f93eeRImPcpUA&quot;&gt;Bitmex Reserach&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_62FowZPxGB6ysv4mcj20A/playlists&quot;&gt;402 Payment Required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/WorldCryptoNetwork/videos&quot;&gt;World Crypto Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCOLeHoKV7SHwAAS0zBwsV-A/videos&quot;&gt;SF Bitcoin Meetup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Live and recorded video from the largest Bitcoin meetup in the United States, in San Francisco, California. Learn from the various speakers we host about top…
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/BitcoinFoundation/videos&quot;&gt;The Bitcoin Foundation&lt;/a&gt;
We approach that mission with Bitcoin’s technology and community as our focus. There is tremendous potential in Bitcoin—from the opportunities it creates for…
&lt;a href=&quot;https://citizenbitcoin.world/episodes&quot;&gt;Episodes | Citizen Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;assorted&quot;&gt;Assorted&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;@TFTC21
@curatingcrypto
@Coinboyspodcast
️@BottomshelfBTC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blockworksgroup.io/blog&quot;&gt;BlockWorks Blog&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Helping To Bridge The Language Gap Between Traditional Finance And The Digital Asset Ecosystem Through Conferences, Private Dinners, and Podcasts&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://noded.org/podcast/noded-090-with-jameson-lopp/&quot;&gt;Noded 0.9.0 with Jameson Lopp&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Pierre Rochard has a freewheeling conversation with Jameson Lopp about everything Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CitizenBitcoin/status/1164983992099233793&quot;&gt;Brady (@CitizenBitcoin)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;1/ The quantity and quality of bitcoin pods has mooned. We really crushed it this bear market and we’re ready for the next wave.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;A thread of my favorite bitcoin pods, why I listen, a link to a choice episode from each, and how I manage to consume so damn much audio c…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CitizenBitcoin/status/1164984010969354241?s=20&quot;&gt;Brady (@CitizenBitcoin)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;12/ @bennd77 - David’s Bitcoin And… podcast is a like @TheCryptoconomy but for bitcoin news. He does 2-3 episodes a week and it’s a great way to stay current. He’s a smart dude who also sometimes drops some fascinating tangents. Here’s the latest ep! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ljWNavM&quot;&gt;https://t.co/ljWNavM&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@dhsue&quot;&gt;Derek Hsue – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Read writing from Derek Hsue on Medium. Investment team @BlockchainCapital, @Wharton. Every day, Derek Hsue and thousands of other voices read, write, and share important stories on Medium.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC5sgoRfoSp3jeX4DEqKLwKg&quot;&gt;Blockchain at Berkeley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://letstalkbitcoin.com/blog/post/ltb-373-bitcoin-etfs-and-the-mainstream-moment&quot;&gt;LTB #373 Bitcoin ETFs and the Mainstream Moment?&lt;/a&gt;
On Todays Episode of Let’s Talk Bitcoin… Andreas Antonopoulos, Stephanie Murphy, Jonathan Mohan and Adam B. Levine are joined by returning guest Caitlin Long for an in-depth discussion of the fascination with, and implications of, bitcoin or cryptocurrency ETFs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/saifedean/status/1034122070597226497&quot;&gt;Saifedean Ammous (@saifedean)&lt;/a&gt;
I’m producing the monthly Bitcoin Standard Research Bulletin. The first issue will be sent out next week. You can subscribe with Bitcoin! More details here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ncDwbVY0LI&quot;&gt;https://t.co/ncDwbVY0LI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://offthechain.libsyn.com/&quot;&gt;Off the Chain&lt;/a&gt;
Host Anthony “Pomp” Pompliano talks to some of the most respected names in crypto and Wall Street to find out how intelligent investors from the new and old financial system are thinking about digital assets.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nlw/status/1037814459627126789&quot;&gt;Nathaniel Whittemore (@nlw)&lt;/a&gt;
Yo, @APompliano’s podcasts have been great so far, but &lt;em&gt;easily&lt;/em&gt; the best thing about the approach are the FULL TRANSCRIPTS &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/cbDYr4CmTy&quot;&gt;https://t.co/cbDYr4CmTy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@laurentmt&quot;&gt;LaurentMT – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Read writing from LaurentMT on Medium. Developer of OXT (&lt;a href=&quot;https://oxt.me&quot;&gt;https://oxt.me)&lt;/a&gt;/). Every day, LaurentMT and thousands of other voices read, write, and share important stories on Medium.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://diar.co/&quot;&gt;Diar - The Digital Assets &amp;amp; Regulation Trade Publication&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Weekly Newsletter on Digital Currency, Assets (Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple and other Cryptocurrencies), Enterprise Blockchain, Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC), Payment Processing, FinTech &amp;amp; Regulation.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitcoin.kn/legendary&quot;&gt;Legendary - The Bitcoin Knowledge Podcast&lt;/a&gt;
To help you better understand Bitcoin the top people in the Bitcoin industry are interviewed by Trace Mayer for the Bitcoin Knowledge Podcast.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://noded.org/&quot;&gt;Noded Bitcoin Podcast&lt;/a&gt;
Bitcoin current events, technical news, and commentary with Pierre Rochard and Michael Goldstein.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cryptoconomy.life/&quot;&gt;Cryptoconomy.Life&lt;/a&gt;
The Technology, The Philosophy, The Cypherpunks, and The Life&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@BitcoinMagazine/make-bitcoin-fun-again-47c6837788c3&quot;&gt;Make Bitcoin Fun Again – Bitcoin Magazine – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
As we near Bitcoin’s 10-year anniversary, and the bitcoin price closes in on its 52-week low — marking a decline of over 75 percent…&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinstrategy.io/&quot;&gt;Coinstrategy.io - Bitcoin &amp;amp; Crypto Interviews, Articles&lt;/a&gt;
Bitcoin, Blockchain &amp;amp; Crypto Interviews, Articles &amp;amp; Other Cool Shit! Home of the No BS crytpo news feed.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/shitcoingrave&quot;&gt;ShitcoinGraveyard (@shitcoingrave)&lt;/a&gt;
What we will deliver when we go online: † 3D Graveyard - Tombstones for dead #crypto coins with most important data/numbers + extended view with all available data you could find † Shitcoin Satire Magazine Join our TG &amp;amp; stay tuned! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/6vaLukW4kk&quot;&gt;https://t.co/6vaLukW4kk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.btcandfriends.com/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin &amp;amp; Friends&lt;/a&gt;
The official website of the animated series Bitcoin &amp;amp; Friends!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/btc_holder/status/1139252977477312512?s=12&quot;&gt;TOXIC Hash [🛡⚡🌮 🔑] (@btc_holder)&lt;/a&gt;
@BullBitcoin_ @VampireVladofW is the most underrated bitcoin writer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/casahodl/status/1141027855289278471?s=12&quot;&gt;Casa (@CasaHODL)&lt;/a&gt;
Good Morning Cyberspace! Introducing a new weekly show where @lopp, @AlenaSatoshi, and @jeremyrwelch give a fast 10min rundown of the week’s top stories in cybersecurity. Find out more here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/HcFbnnEQc4&quot;&gt;https://t.co/HcFbnnEQc4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/_joerodgers/status/1142889975270248454?s=20&quot;&gt;Joe Rodgers (@_joerodgers)&lt;/a&gt;
All hail the king… of curation, @nlw! Crypto happens fast. If you want weekly crypto industry news and conversations, sign up for this man’s newsletter. Congrats on 1 year of dedicated curation. Looking forward to what’s next and how you will push content delivery for…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/info/audio-video/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Assorted Technical Topics</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/tech/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;medium-3 medium-push-9 columns&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p id=&quot;toc&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#block-size&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-block-size&quot;&gt;Block Size&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#bips&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-bips&quot;&gt;BIPs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#scripting&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-scripting&quot;&gt;Scripting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#related-posts&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- /.medium-4.columns --&gt;



&lt;div class=&quot;medium-9 medium-pull-3 columns&quot;&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-technical.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-technical.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;On the Technical Side of things… largely unsorted… :)&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@jeremyrubin/8-problems-with-bitcoin-to-solve-before-block-size-6b4d35e0c6f9&quot;&gt;8 Problems for the Bitcoin Community to Solve Before Block Size:&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Recently the debate around block size has been getting a huge amount of attention, and it is easy to think this is the most important issue…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@pierre_rochard/bitcoin-governance-37e86299470f&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Governance - Pierre Rochard - Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/digitalassetresearch/a-guide-to-bitcoins-technical-brilliance-for-non-programmers-e28211e797c0&quot;&gt;A Guide To Bitcoin’s Technical Brilliance (For Non-Programmers)&lt;/a&gt; - 18 minutes is all that it takes to understand Bitcoin better than most people.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@pierre_rochard/understanding-the-technical-side-of-bitcoin-2c212dd65c09&quot;&gt;Understanding the Technical Side of Bitcoin - Pierre Rochard - Medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/xavi_xsb&quot;&gt;XSB 💾 (@xavi_xsb)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;To my surprise the last @bitcoinoptech newsletter mentions a very small pull request I made that recently got merged into LND. Bitcoin Optech Newsletter is by far the best source of information for the latest fixes and features. Subscribe if you manage Bitcoin nodes.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinops.org/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Optech&lt;/a&gt; - (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bitcoinoptech&quot;&gt;@bitcoinoptech&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcointechweekly.com/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Tech Weekly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lx9zgZCMqXE&quot;&gt;How Bitcoin Works Under the Hood&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;A somewhat technical explanation of how Bitcoin works. Want more? Check out my new in-depth course on the latest in Bitcoin, Blockchain, and a survey of the …&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://noded.org/podcast/noded-010-with-david-harding/&quot;&gt;Noded 0.1.0 with David Harding&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Michael Goldstein and Pierre Rochard have a conversation with David Harding about hard forks, Ethereum, MAST, Simplicity, and Scaling Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://noded.org/podcast/noded-0490-with-andrew-poelstra/&quot;&gt;Noded 0.49.0 with Andrew Poelstra&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Michael Goldstein and Pierre Rochard talk with Andrew Poelstra from Blockstream about Miniscript, Liquid, Schnorr, Taproot, and other Bitcoin voodoo.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SebastienGllmt/status/1060744966618529793&quot;&gt;Sebastien Guillemot (@SebastienGllmt)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Wow this is awesome! Check out this slide deck about the Bitcoin Backbone Model. The math used in this paper is reused in a bunch of papers about crypto (including Cardano) so understanding this will help you understand all the other papers! https://t.co/lUb3NVaOi4&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lx9zgZCMqXE&quot;&gt;How Bitcoin Works Under the Hood&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;A somewhat technical explanation of how Bitcoin works. Want more? Check out my new in-depth course on the latest in Bitcoin, Blockchain, and a survey of the&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://eprint.iacr.org/2015/578.pdf&quot;&gt;Tampering with the Delivery of Blocks and Transactions in Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ethz.ch/content/dam/ethz/special-interest/infk/inst-infsec/system-security-group-dam/research/publications/pub2015/tissec15_karame.pdf&quot;&gt;Misbehavior in Bitcoin: A Study of Double-Spending and Accountability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@nopara73/stealing-satoshis-bitcoins-cc4d57919a2b&quot;&gt;Who Will Steal Satoshi’s Bitcoins? – nopara73&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;I woke up in the middle of the night so I fired up Twitter and I encountered two well-known cryptographers’ conversation about quantum…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1200/0*GWRYyGRclAs1rC4K.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.apograf.io/articles/13486&quot;&gt;Okamoto Beats Schnorr: On the Provable Security of Multi-Signatures&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The insecurity discussion starts near the bottom of page 2 of the paper The security issues the paper discusses are pretty simple to solve theoretically, but they all increase the communication complexity of the signing schemes from O(n^2) to O(n^3) Which means there’s that many more points at which the multisig can be sabotaged or an error of some sort can occur Which basically means that all of those schemes are useless for large numbers of participants Not that they were that useful for any significant number of participants with a complexity of O(n^2)&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/adddja/the_weird_nonce_pattern/&quot;&gt;r/Bitcoin - The weird nonce pattern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://external-preview.redd.it/tRXRLScPWuo9RGJ6m_AOX_1PvvMsOkfYJSVMZznw19Y.jpg?auto=webp&amp;amp;s=fdb00a52ceb4db3f69cb5e6006e4b426410c48a9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YSUVRj8iznU&quot;&gt;Taproot, and Schnorr, and SIGHASH_NOINPUT, oh my!&lt;/a&gt; - Pieter Wuille, Bitcoin Core developer and Blockstream co-founder, spoke about Taproot, Schnorr, and SIGHASH_NOINPUT.
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;In this talk Pieter went into the benefits of these ideas and discussed an upcoming proposal for a first step that combines a subset of these ideas. Some ideas will be left for future extensions, in order to avoid complexity and limiting the design space. Yet, this would bring privacy and flexibility benefits to Bitcoin, as well as moderate scaling advantages. The main focus is Taproot, which has the potential to make all outputs look identical, by merging pay-to-pubkey and pay-to-scripthash into one - but other changes will be needed to make it widely applicable and efficient.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;[Slides](https://prezi.com/view/YkJwE7LYJzAzJw9g1bWV/&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/979jhq/to_everyone_rushing_back_into_btc_from_altcoins/&quot;&gt;To everyone rushing back into BTC from altcoins: What matters is that you learn why Bitcoin needs to be conservative in its development.&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Over the past year, the prevailing thought among many in the cryptocurrency communities is that bitcoin is not keeping up with other coins. That somehow bitcoin was being intentionally crippled, or that the developers did not know what they were doing. As we are seeing with the bitcoin dominance going up, that prevailing thought was wrong. The coins who were supposedly going to kill bitcoin have been all but abandoned in many cases. Many others are in the process of dying a slow death (which may take years to fully play out).&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1UthKYsC7B7uD0V32beZ1puC0n0vzHg2SYFcTBqdbiOM/edit?fbclid=IwAR3QTY6N4o-D7ihJS0pEWvCzQUkH3bAVdwQ7O7zbRhjNMxSese9gnj4-A50#slide=id.p&quot;&gt;The Blockchain Backbone Model&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Today I gave a talk about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/dionyziz/status/1060646354068930561&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Backbone model&lt;/a&gt;, the first mathematical theory to prove bitcoin is secure, invented by @sol3gga, Nikos Leonardos and Juan Garay. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SebastienGllmt/status/1060744966618529793&quot;&gt;*&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;block-size&quot;&gt;Block Size&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@jeremyrubin/8-problems-with-bitcoin-to-solve-before-block-size-6b4d35e0c6f9&quot;&gt;8 Problems for the Bitcoin Community to Solve Before Block Size&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Recently the debate around block size has been getting a huge amount of attention, and it is easy to think this is the most important…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;bips&quot;&gt;BIPs&lt;/h3&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coindoo.com/what-is-a-bip-the-most-famous-bitcoin-improvement-proposals/&quot;&gt;https://coindoo.com/what-is-a-bip-the-most-famous-bitcoin-improvement-proposals/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coindoo.com/author/vladimirciobica/&quot;&gt;Vladimir Ciobica&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;table&gt;
      &lt;tbody&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td&gt;[What Is a BIP?&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td&gt;The Most Famous Bitcoin Improvement Proposals - C…](https://coindoo.com/what-is-a-bip-the-most-famous-bitcoin-improvement-proposals/)&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;/tbody&gt;
    &lt;/table&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;There are some that argue that these BIPs can and will eventually lead to more forks in the network which is generally considered to be a bag thing in the cryptocurrency community at large.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;⧉infominer 22-Jul-19 03:34 AM&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoin/bips/blob/master/bip-0042.mediawiki&quot;&gt;https://github.com/bitcoin/bips/blob/master/bip-0042.mediawiki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoin/bips/blob/master/bip-0042.mediawiki&quot;&gt;bitcoin/bips&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Improvement Proposals.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h2 id=&quot;scripting&quot;&gt;Scripting&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fc16.ifca.ai/bitcoin/papers/MES16.pdf&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Covenants&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Abstract.This paper presents an extension to Bitcoin’s script language enabling covenants, a primitive that allows transactions to restrict howthe value they transfer is used in the future. Covenants expand the set offinancial instruments expressible in Bitcoin, and enable new powerful andnovel use cases. We illustrate two novel security constructs built usingcovenants.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/yes-bitcoin-can-do-smart-contracts-and-particl-demonstrates-how/&quot;&gt;Yes, Bitcoin Can Do Smart Contracts and Particl Demonstrates How&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The Bitcoin blockchain is not known for its ability to enable smart contracts. In fact, most developers creating smart contracts use a different blockchain, like Ethereum. But the truth is that the Bitcoin protocol can be used to create smart contracts. Particl.io, the blockc…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/scriptless-scripts-how-bitcoin-can-support-smart-contracts-without-smart-contracts/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Magazine - Scriptless Scripts: How Bitcoin Can Support Smart Contracts&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin’s capacity is limited. Meanwhile, smart contracts can be resource intensive. So even though Bitcoin has always supported basic smart contract functionality, the two have never been a natural match.But a recent topic of research spearheaded by Blockstream mathematici…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lopp/status/1072156493116518400&quot;&gt;Jameson Lopp (@lopp)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/etW1yP65Zr&quot;&gt;https://t.co/etW1yP65Zr&lt;/a&gt; has a neat animated Bitcoin script interpreter and debugger for those who want to better understand script execution. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/5TAkdoPU7b&quot;&gt;https://t.co/5TAkdoPU7b&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/6UkzUGu4dK&quot;&gt;https://t.co/6UkzUGu4dK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/liuhongchao/bitcoin4s&quot;&gt;liuhongchao/bitcoin4s&lt;/a&gt;- A Bitcoin Script interpreter and debugger in Scala - liuhongchao/bitcoin4s&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChristopherA/status/1154460495279058944?s=20&quot;&gt;Christopher Allen (@ChristopherA)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;I’m not suggesting that Russel’s Simplicity toolchain is for securing Unix bootstrap, instead focus is to secure future blockchain script languages. However, it does seem that it too can support Scheme-like script atoms, and lessons from it could be leveraged beyond bl…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChristopherA/status/1154457284078030849?s=20&quot;&gt;Christopher Allen (@ChristopherA)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Interesting, some of these approaches toward “Reduced Binary Seed” make use of minimized Scheme, which is also a potential target for Russel O’Connor’s of @Blockstream’s provable Simplicy toolchain, which can maybe probably secure each of the Scheme atoms. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t/&quot;&gt;https://t&lt;/a&gt;….&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/WebOfTrustInfo/rwot1-sf/blob/master/final-documents/smart-signatures.pdf&quot;&gt;WebOfTrustInfo/rwot1-sf - Smart Signatures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/WebOfTrustInfo/rwot2-id2020/blob/master/draft-documents/smarter-signatures.md&quot;&gt;WebOfTrustInfo/rwot2-id2020 - Smarter Signatures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ElementsProject/simplicity&quot;&gt;ElementsProject/simplicity&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Simplicity is a blockchain programming language designed as an alternative to Bitcoin script. - ElementsProject/simplicity&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h2 id=&quot;related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/security/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Security Info + Best Practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assorted Technical Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/privacy/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy and Bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/lightning/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin - Layer 2 - Lightning, Liquid and Beyond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-1/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Layer 1 - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/decentralization/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li class=&quot;text-right&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/feed/archive/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More ›&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;


  
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/tech/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Privacy and Bitcoin</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/info/privacy/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;medium-3 medium-push-9 columns&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p id=&quot;toc&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#info&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-info&quot;&gt;Info&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#cryptoconomy-quickreads&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-cryptoconomy-quickreads&quot;&gt;Cryptoconomy QuickReads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#wallets&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-wallets&quot;&gt;Wallets&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#mixers&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-mixers&quot;&gt;Mixers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#digital-privacy&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-digital-privacy&quot;&gt;Digital Privacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#related-posts&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- /.medium-4.columns --&gt;



&lt;div class=&quot;medium-9 medium-pull-3 columns&quot;&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-privacy.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-privacy.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coincache.net/2019/01/02/bitcoin-anonymity-guide-2019-how-to-use-btc-like-a-straight-up-g/?v=3e8d115eb4b3&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Anonymity Guide 2019: How to use BTC like a straight up G&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gir.pub/deepdotweb/jolly-rogers-security-guide-for-beginners/&quot;&gt;Jolly Roger’s Security Guide for Beginners - Deep Dot Web&lt;/a&gt; (old, but, perhaps still worth a read)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://99bitcoins.com/buy-bitcoin/anonymously-without-id/&quot;&gt;Buying and Using Bitcoin Anonymously Without ID (2019 Updated)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://link.medium.com/hYHYNewq9Y&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Security Brief Volume 1 with Dhruv Bansal&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;One of the most often overlooked aspects to owning Bitcoin is how to safely secure and store it. Most people have their own best practices…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Privacy&quot;&gt;en.bitcoin.it/wiki/Privacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/6102bitcoin/FAQ/blob/master/hodl-privacy.md&quot;&gt;Privacy for HODLers @6102Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.openbitcoinprivacyproject.org/&quot;&gt;Open Bitcoin Privacy Project - Accelerating Progress to Our Financial Future&lt;/a&gt;
The Open Bitcoin Privacy Project is an open source, global organization whose mission is to improve financial privacy within the Bitcoin ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bitcoin.com/how-to-buy-bitcoin-without-disclosing-your-identity&quot;&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin Without Disclosing Your Identity - Bitcoin News&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Privacy preservation is one of cryptocurrency’s defining characteristics. Digital assets such as bitcoin provide a far higher degree of anonymity and surety than traditional online payment methods such as credit card or Paypal. There’s just one problem: buying bitcoin wit…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h2 id=&quot;info&quot;&gt;Info&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thebitcoinnews.com/cypherpunk-essentials-a-beginners-guide-to-crypto-privacy&quot;&gt;Cypherpunk Essentials: A Beginner’s Guide to Crypto Privacy - Th…&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The following op-ed on crypto privacy was written by Reuben Yap. He is the Chief Operations Officer of Zcoin. A corporate lawyer for ten years, specializing in institutional frameworks, Reuben founded one of SE Asia’s top VPN companies, bolehvpn.net. He graduated with a LL…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@thecryptoconomy/dandelions-and-a-bright-future-for-bitcoin-privacy-712dbc4b1ec5&quot;&gt;Dandelions, and a Bright Future for Bitcoin Privacy&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_100---Dandelions-and-a-Bright-Future-for-Bitcoin-Privacy-e2ndrg&quot;&gt;CryptoQuikRead_100&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/bitcoin-privacycoin-tech-making-bitcoin-more-private/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Magazine - Bitcoin as a Privacycoin: This Tech is Making Bitcoin More Private&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_149---Bitcoin-as-a-PrivacyCoin-e2ndpr&quot;&gt;CryptoQuikRead_149&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is not really private - but these projects are making significant improvements to Bitcoin privacy.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mdudas/status/1165745781862780929?s=12&quot;&gt;Mike Dudas (@mdudas)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Using transaction data, investigators trace dark-web transaction using bitcoin to defendant’s exchange address and district court orders detention &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/Il3gdNkvLq&quot;&gt;https://t.co/Il3gdNkvLq&lt;/a&gt; via @NelsonMRosario&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;cryptoconomy-quickreads&quot;&gt;Cryptoconomy QuickReads&lt;/h3&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_085 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_085---Increasing-Bitcoin-Privacy-Using-the-Lightning-Network-e2ndru&quot;&gt;Increasing Bitcoin Privacy Using the Lightning Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_165 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_165---Why-Privacy-Matters-e2ndp9&quot;&gt;Why Privacy Matters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoChat_12 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoChat_12---Talking-Privacy--Bitcoin--the-New-Economy-with-the-Raleigh-Bitcoin-Meetup-e4ar2g&quot;&gt;Talking Privacy, Bitcoin &amp;amp; the New Economy with the Raleigh Bitcoin Meetup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_227 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_227---Bitcoin-is-a-Hedge-Against-the-Cashless-Society-e3l5ne&quot;&gt;Bitcoin is a Hedge Against the Cashless Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h2 id=&quot;wallets&quot;&gt;Wallets&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@nopara73/wasabi-privacy-focused-bitcoin-wallet-for-desktop-3962d567045a&quot;&gt;Wasabi: Privacy Focused Bitcoin Wallet for Desktop – nopara73 …&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;A few days ago I gave a talk at the Building on Bitcoin conference, where I unveiled Wasabi Wallet that will bring Bitcoin Privacy to a…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_112 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_112---Wasabi-Privacy-Focused-Bitcoin-Wallet-e2ndr4&quot;&gt;Wasabi Privacy Focused Bitcoin Wallet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;mixers&quot;&gt;Mixers&lt;/h3&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thebitcoinnews.com/bestmixer-ios-bitcoin-blender-aims-to-bring-anonymity-back-to-crypto/&quot;&gt;BestMixer.io’s Bitcoin Blender Aims to Bring Anonymity Back to C…&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The BestMixer.io development team has introduced their next generation bitcoin blender in an effort aimed at disrupting the quickening pace of blockchain analysis firms such as Chainalysis. The reason behind the move is simple: cryptocurrency is not anonymous but it pretends …&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/az9rap/bitcoin_mixers/&quot;&gt;r/Bitcoin - Bitcoin mixers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@nopara73/samourai-vs-wasabi-mixing-architecture-18b92b3ca17b&quot;&gt;Samourai vs Wasabi Mixing Architecture&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;You have 3.5BTC that you want to mix with either Whirlpool or with Wasabi. For the sake of comparison, I assume 1BTC base denominations…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/6102bitcoin/status/1187623411343867905?s=20&quot;&gt;6102Bitcoin (@6102bitcoin)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;@nopara73 Take your time. Read these articles. + “Diving head first into Whirlpool Anonymity Sets.” by Samourai Wallet &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/sckMsP2tyI&quot;&gt;https://t.co/sckMsP2tyI&lt;/a&gt; + “Tracking the PlusToken Whale: Attempted Bitcoin Mixing and Its Impact on Wasabi Wallet” by ErgoBTC &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/hAev&quot;&gt;https://t.co/hAev&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_138 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_138---Traditional-Bitcoin-Mixers-e2ndq5&quot;&gt;Traditional Bitcoin Mixers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thebitcoinnews.com/bestmixer-ios-bitcoin-blender-aims-to-bring-anonymity-back-to-crypto/&quot;&gt;BestMixer.io’s Bitcoin Blender Aims to Bring Anonymity Back to C…&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The BestMixer.io development team has introduced their next generation bitcoin blender in an effort aimed at disrupting the quickening pace of blockchain analysis firms such as Chainalysis. The reason behind the move is simple: cryptocurrency is not anonymous but it pretends …&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://leastauthority.com/blog/mixnet-intro/&quot;&gt;Introduction to Mix Networks and Anonymous Communication Networks …&lt;/a&gt;
Least Authority was formed in 2011 to create freedom-compatible technologies. We are a small team who believe that freedom matters in Internet technology. You can take advantage of online services while retaining control over your own data. We’re here to make it easy.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/bitcoin-privacy.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h2 id=&quot;digital-privacy&quot;&gt;Digital Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not Specific to Bitcoin&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SarahJamieLewis/status/1026340294818582533&quot;&gt;Sarah Jamie Lewis (@SarahJamieLewis)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;If you are waiting for a government to give you meaningful privacy from surveillance you are going to be waiting a long time. Privacy is consent. Consent is, unfortunately, something that you sometimes have to enforce.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lopp/status/1026139157125640192&quot;&gt;Jameson Lopp (@lopp)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The cost of maintaining one’s privacy continues to rise as the cost of surveillance technology continues to fall. Most folks have neither the time nor the money to properly protect their privacy these days. Cypherpunks are the intolerant minority, the Spartans defending th…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://research.stlouisfed.org/publications/review/2018/07/16/payment-systems-and-privacy&quot;&gt;Payment Systems and Privacy&lt;/a&gt;  by Charles Kahn - 2018-07-16
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Abstract: Privacy in payments is desired not just for illegal transactions, but also for protection from malfeasance or negligence by counterparties or by the payments system provider itself. Proposals to abolish cash take inadequate account of these legitimate demands for privacy. While central banks can play a useful role in setting standards for payments privacy, they are unlikely to have a comparative advantage at providing privacy. Therefore the replacement of cash by central bank electronic money is likely to spur demand for alternative means of payments to solve specific privacy problems.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.privacytools.io/&quot;&gt;Privacy Tools | Encryption against global mass surveillance&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;You are being watched! Knowledge, encryption and privacy tools to protect you against global mass surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aclu.org/blog/national-security/secrecy/you-may-have-nothing-hide-you-still-have-something-fear&quot;&gt;You May Have ‘Nothing to Hide’ But You Still Have Something to Fear&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;This post was first published on MSNBC.com.In the wake of recent news that the NSA is spying on Americans, I have been particularly struck by the argument that “if you’ve got nothing to hide, you’ve got nothing to fear.”At first blush, this argument might seem sound – after…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nothing_to_hide_argument&quot;&gt;Nothing to hide argument - wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The nothing to hide argument states that government surveillance programs do not threaten privacy unless they uncover illegal activities, and that if they do uncover illegal activities, the person committing these activities does not have the right to keep them private. Hence…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lopp/status/1048382404459724800&quot;&gt;Jameson Lopp (@lopp)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;“It’s possible to measure the scalability of a system, but it’s impossible to empirically evaluate privacy - we have to resort to thought experiments. As such, it’s quite challenging to decide upon privacy and scalability trade-offs.” - @secparam #ScalingBitcoin&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/errorinn/status/1048723006271381504&quot;&gt;Erinn Atwater (@errorinn)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;i want an internet where my privacy can’t be invaded by third parties, but also i don’t have to run my own damn server for everything. just got step one working: send a file! p2p with bidirectional authentication, metadata resistance, and easy verified contact management&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ryerson.ca/pbdce/certification/seven-foundational-principles-of-privacy-by-design&quot;&gt;The Seven Foundational Principles of Privacy by Design&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Privacy by Design is a concept Dr. Ann Cavoukian developed back in the 90’s, to address the ever-growing and systemic effects of Information and Communication Technologies, and of large-scale networked data systems.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChristopherA/status/1090791869313736704&quot;&gt;Christopher Allen (@ChristopherA)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;I highly suggest more of the #RebootingWebOfTrust community, the W3C Credentials CG, and the broader decentralized web community read this book and support @SarahJamieLewis by paying for a copy. But read it! Being LGBTA may not be your reason for privacy, but similar probl…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ghacks.net/&quot;&gt;gHacks Technology News&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Ghacks Technology News is a tech blog that reviews software, apps, Internet services, and offers tips and tricks about Windows, Android, and other systems.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/piratebeachbum/status/1136023941703770117?s=12&quot;&gt;Pirate Beachbum (@piratebeachbum)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;For all you privacy freaks, here is a must read that validates any sense of privacy we think we have has been compromised the last 20 plus years. It’s worse than you ever imagined!&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=20206536&quot;&gt;The CIA Spied on People Through Their Smart TVs, Leaked Documents Reveal (2017)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=20267562&quot;&gt;When Myspace Was King, Employees Abused a Tool Called ‘Overlord’ to Spy on Users&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/esultanik/status/1129026681291911168?s=12&quot;&gt;Evan Sultanik (@ESultanik)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Telegram is &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; the solution. Friends don’t let friends use Telegram. This’ll be a thread! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ogHmNZkOg4&quot;&gt;https://t.co/ogHmNZkOg4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://caitlin-long.com/2018/06/28/supreme-court-and-digital-privacy-should-blockchain-companies-challenge-the-bank-secrecy-act/&quot;&gt;Supreme Court and Digital Privacy: Should Blockchain Companies Cha…&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Digital privacy law experts predict a flood of litigation testing the constitutionality of government data collection practices after the Supreme Court’s Carpenter decision on cell phone data…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://brave.com/vpn0-a-privacy-preserving-distributed-virtual-private-network/&quot;&gt;VPN⁰: A Privacy-Preserving Distributed Virtual Private Network |…&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Distributed virtual private networks (dVPNs) are a new form of VPN with no central authority. In a dVPN, users are both VPN clients and relay/exit nodes as in a Peer-to-Peer (P2P) network. While dVPNs make strong privacy claims, they also carry the risk that a user will inadv…&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=21169768&quot;&gt;VPN⁰: A Privacy-Preserving Distributed VPN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h2 id=&quot;related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/security/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Security Info + Best Practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assorted Technical Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/privacy/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy and Bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/lightning/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin - Layer 2 - Lightning, Liquid and Beyond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-1/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Layer 1 - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/decentralization/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li class=&quot;text-right&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/feed/archive/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More ›&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;


  
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/info/privacy/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Lightning - Info</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/layer-2/lightning/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;medium-3 medium-push-9 columns&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p id=&quot;toc&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#info&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-info&quot;&gt;💡 info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#media&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-media&quot;&gt;💡 media&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#cryptoconomy-podcast&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-cryptoconomy-podcast&quot;&gt;Cryptoconomy Podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#lapps&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-lapps&quot;&gt;LApps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#related-posts&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- /.medium-4.columns --&gt;



&lt;div class=&quot;medium-9 medium-pull-3 columns&quot;&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-lightningfo.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-lightningfo.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/NickSzabo4/status/846492284036145152&quot;&gt;Nick Szabo⚡️ (@NickSzabo4)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;“Bitcoin .. needs .. a secondary level of payment[s] which is lighter weight.” – Hal Finney 2010 https://t.co/tIbkVF2ezc ht @rextar4444&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@timevalueofbtc/the-bitcoin-second-layer-d503949d0a06&quot;&gt;The Bitcoin Second Layer – Nik Bhatia – Medium The Lightning Network Reference Rate&lt;/a&gt;, Part 1 of 4&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/danheld/status/1033044447842336768&quot;&gt;Dan Hedl (@danheld)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;1/ A complete debunking of top Lightning FUD claims:&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.archive.org/web/20180820184635/https://the-lightning-times.ongoodbits.com/2018/08/20/issue-1&quot;&gt;The Lightning Times - Issue #1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/pierre_rochard/status/1055159992733626368&quot;&gt;Pierre Rochard [⚡️] (@pierre_rochard)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The LND node software now runs from within the Excel plugin. With neutrino, that means that a Windows + Excel user can be making and receiving LN payments with a few clicks. https://t.co/qeP2dCJSqp&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/btc/status/1052973003867271168&quot;&gt;#Bitcoin doesn’t compete with Visa. #Lightning does. ⚡️⚡️⚡️&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/wbobeirne/status/1131989707389329408?s=12&quot;&gt;Will O’Beirne (@wbobeirne)&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Need plans for the long weekend? Why not get started on making your own Lightning App! Over the next couple of weeks I’ll be posting a 5 part series on building a modern web app that takes lightning payments, and how to host it securely. https://t.co/gDsAAUKrnj&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/fulmolightning/status/1035183579196743680&quot;&gt;Fulmo ⚡ @fulmolightning&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Get ready to rumble! The latest batch of 20 #RaspiBlitz, a full #Bitcoin and #LightningNetwork node running on a Raspberry Pi, is ready to be picked up and plugged in at the #LightningHackday! If you can’t attend in person, you can build one yourself:&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;https://github.com/rootzoll/raspiblitz
&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/edaW3pO.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lightning.engineering/posts/2018/05/30/routing.html&quot;&gt;Exploring Lightning Network Routing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;When we last left our hero Carol, she had successfully joined the Lightning Network and started making Lightning transactions. As she’s become familiar with the user experience side of Lightning, she’s also started to become more interested in Lightning from a technical standpoint. She’s even thinking about running a Lightning routing node herself, with the goal of earning enough in routing fees to pay for her monthly BitFlix subscription.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephanlivera/status/1028079725460111360&quot;&gt;Stephan Livera (@stephanlivera)&lt;/a&gt; -(&lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/episode/7eq7H9t54IvnLo4QKA9rrb&quot;&gt;spotify&lt;/a&gt;)
SLP9 - Lightning UX and Routing, with @bvu VP, Product of @lightning We discuss: - Lightning User Experience - Lightning Routing - Benefits for users, merchants and exchanges - Autopilot, watchtowers, AMP, splicing listen, subscribe, share!&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/casa/announcing-the-casa-lightning-node-596df7a7427&quot;&gt;Announcing the Casa Lightning Node – Casa Blog – Medium&lt;/a&gt; -The easiest way to use Lightning available today.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Ragnarly/status/1039113181023490050&quot;&gt;𝑅𝑎𝑔𝑛𝑎𝑟 𝐿𝑖𝑓𝑡ℎ𝑟𝑎𝑠𝑖𝑟 🏴 (@Ragnarly)&lt;/a&gt; -Some of the best tools in bitcoin have been built by without raising capital from VCs: @BtcpayServer, @SamouraiWallet, @OPENDIME and @COLDCARDwallet, and most software wallets. Did I miss any?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Beautyon_/status/1062100915925213185&quot;&gt;Beautyon (@Beautyon_)&lt;/a&gt; -SUPER INTERESTING: “The 8333.io platform provides tooling, apps &amp;amp; services on top of any bip32 compatible Bitcoin wallet. It’s a service layer on top of the Bitcoin network, offering powerful utilities for users and/or developpers.” https://8333.io/&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://shea.io/lightning-in-2018&quot;&gt;Lightning in 2018&lt;/a&gt;
-Below is an archived and reformatted tweetstorm from Nov 29, 2018. Enjoy! #1 Lightning Network is on fire lately 12500 channels (up 3…&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stephanlivera.com/episode/37&quot;&gt;SLP37 Rene Pickhardt – Bitcoin Lightning Education &amp;amp; Lightning S…&lt;/a&gt;
Rene Pickhardt, a Bitcoin/Lightning educator, and rising star in the world of Lightning joins me to talk about the Lightning Network. We discuss: How he got into Lightning Involvement in the Pirate…&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/blockstream-boosts-bitcoin-satellite-service-with-lightning-payments&quot;&gt;Blockstream Boosts Bitcoin Satellite Service With Lightning Payments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@melik_87377/lightning-network-enables-unicast-transactions-in-bitcoin-lightning-is-bitcoins-tcp-ip-stack-8ec1d42c14f5&quot;&gt;Lightning Network enables Unicast Transactions in Bitcoin.&lt;/a&gt;
It has recently come to my attention that there is a great deal of confusion revolving around the Lightning Network within the Bitcoin and…&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realLudvigArt/status/1037592389529919488&quot;&gt;Melik Manukyan ⚡️ ludvigart.com (@realLudvigArt)&lt;/a&gt;
1)I am seeing an increasing number of people under the impression that #lightning as an overlay bridge network for #blockchains (via atomic swaps) is a great thing for alts. And they can not be more wrong. In reality, Lightning is where #altcoins will come in droves only…&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scipioerp.com/2018/12/12/is-lightning-ready-for-commerce/&quot;&gt;Is the Lightning network ready for commerce?&lt;/a&gt;
We have been experimenting with Lightning (Bitcoin) payments. But is it ready for commerce applications? Here’s what we think…&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/alexbosworth/status/1078353292768403456&quot;&gt;Alex Bosworth ☇ (@alexbosworth)&lt;/a&gt;
          &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Ways I can tell LN routing is not a mature market yet: - I’m charging 25x more than anyone and routing more than ever before - The largest capacity owner assigns capacity at random - Almost no one charges any fees at all for routing - Most public nodes aren’t even reli…&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/timevalueofbtc/status/1078337607493332992&quot;&gt;Nik Bhatia (@timevalueofbtc)&lt;/a&gt; 
Recent interviews given by @roasbeef @bitconner and tweets by @alexbosworth confirm my initial theory about the potential for operating a profitable Lightning node: payment channel management skill is the primary driver of profits. Merely staking capital ensures nothing.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lists.linuxfoundation.org/pipermail/lightning-dev/2018-December/001752.html&quot;&gt;[Lightning-dev] An Argument For Single-Asset Lightning Network&lt;/a&gt;
In theory, the Lightning Network could potentially perform “seamless” currency conversions, allowing a payer to spend one currency to pay a payee requesting for another currency.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;However, a significant technical barrier prevents implementation of such feature as of current designs (late 2018) for Lightning.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;info&quot;&gt;💡 info&lt;/h3&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coincenter.org/entry/making-sense-of-lightning-network-nodes-and-money-transmission-licensing&quot;&gt;Making sense of Lightning network nodes and money transmission licensing&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;An update on Coin Center’s work to avoid unnecessary regulatory burdens on technologists.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/lightning-power-users/windows-macos-lightning-network-284bd5034340&quot;&gt;Easiest Bitcoin Lightning Guide!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@The1Brand7/lightning-faq-67bd2b957d70&quot;&gt;#Bitcoin Lightning Network FAQ&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Q 1: What is the Lightning Network?&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ion.radar.tech/&quot;&gt;Radar ION - Your guide to the Lightning Network&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Master the Lightning Network with our app and wallet recommendations, developer and troubleshooting tools, Lightning wiki, getting started tutorials, and more!&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;media&quot;&gt;💡 media&lt;/h3&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/djseeds/lncast&quot;&gt;djseeds/lncast&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;LNCast - Lightning Network Podcatcher.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lncast.com/&quot;&gt;LNCast&lt;/a&gt;
Lightning Network Podcasts&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://noded.org/podcast/&quot;&gt;noded.org/podcast&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin current events, technical news, and commentary with Pierre Rochard and Michael Goldstein.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stephanlivera.com/episodes&quot;&gt;stephanlivera.com/episodes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://talesfromthecrypt.libsyn.com/&quot;&gt;Tales from the Crypt: A Bitcoin Podcast&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Tales from the Crypt is a podcast hosted by Marty Bent about Bitcoin. Join Marty, Editor in Chief of “the best newsletter in crypto”, as he sits down to discuss Bitcoin with interesting people.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/show/5raGruI7FqmwCKY0l2sSuR&quot;&gt;The Coin Pod&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;A series of conversations about Bitcoin with people who build, study, and use it, hosted weekly by Zack Voell. by The YMB Network&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whatbitcoindid.com/lightning-network-special&quot;&gt;Lightning Network Special: What Bitcoin Did&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@ACINQ&quot;&gt;ACINQ – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Read writing from ACINQ on Medium. We are building an implementation of Lightning, a scalable instant payment network built on top of the Bitcoin blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/meetbitfury/tagged/lightning-network&quot;&gt;Lightning Network – Meet Bitfury – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Read writing about Lightning Network in Meet Bitfury. Learn more about Bitfury, the leading full-service blockchain technology company.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blockstream.com/categories/lightning-network/&quot;&gt;blockstream.com/categories/lightning-network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/lightning-resources&quot;&gt;Lightning Resources – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;An information page about the Lightning Network protocol, a scalable transaction cache layer for Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lopp.net/lightning-information.html&quot;&gt;Jameson Lopp’s Lightning Network Resources&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;A comprehensive guide to educational Lightning Network information &amp;amp; resources.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@rusty_lightning&quot;&gt;Rusty Russell – Medium&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Read writing from Rusty Russell on Medium. Rusty is a Linux kernel dev who wandered into Blockstream, and is currently trying to produce a prototype and spec for bitcoin lightning. Hodls bitcoin (only).&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-dyor-podcast-blockchain-bitcoin-cryptocurrency/id1469404703?i=1000442180425&quot;&gt;‎The DYOR Podcast - Blockchain, Bitcoin &amp;amp; Cryptocurrency: Lightn…&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;‎Show The DYOR Podcast - Blockchain, Bitcoin &amp;amp; Cryptocurrency, Ep Lightning Network, Private Keys and Bitcoin Nodes with Jameson Lopp- DYOR 002 - Jun 19, 2019&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;cryptoconomy-podcast&quot;&gt;Cryptoconomy Podcast&lt;/h3&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@melik_87377/lightning-network-enables-unicast-transactions-in-bitcoin-lightning-is-bitcoins-tcp-ip-stack-8ec1d42c14f5&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/k55OjEO.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_011 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_011---Lightning-Enables-Unicast-Transactions-in-Bitcoin-e2nduh&quot;&gt;Lightning Enables Unicast Transactions in Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_027 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_027---The-Barely-Discussed--Incredible-Benefit-of-the-Lightning-Network-e2ndu1&quot;&gt;The Barely Discussed, Incredible Benefit of the Lightning Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_047 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_047---Understanding-The-Lightning-Network-Part-1-e2ndtd&quot;&gt;Understanding The Lightning Network Part 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_048 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_048---Understanding-The-Lightning-Network-Part-2-e2ndt4&quot;&gt;Understanding The Lightning Network Part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_049 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_049---Understanding-The-Lightning-Network-Part-3-e2ndtc&quot;&gt;Understanding The Lightning Network Part 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_061 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_061---Eltoo---A-Simplified-Update-Mechanism-for-Lightning-e2ndso&quot;&gt;Eltoo - A Simplified Update Mechanism for Lightning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_062 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_062---This-New-Scaling-Layer-Could-Make-Lightning-More-Effective-e2ndsn&quot;&gt;This New Scaling Layer Could Make Lightning More Effective&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_063 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_063---Atomic-Swaps--How-the-Lightning-Network-Extends-to-Altcoins-e2ndsm&quot;&gt;Atomic Swaps, How the Lightning Network Extends to Altcoins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_064 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_064---The-Future-of-Bitcoin---What-Lightning-Could-Look-Like-e2ndsk&quot;&gt;The Future of Bitcoin - What Lightning Could Look Like&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_065 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_065---Lightning-User-Experience--A-Day-in-the-Life-of-Carol-e2ndsl&quot;&gt;Lightning User Experience, A Day in the Life of Carol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_082 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_082---Exploring-Lightning-Network-Routing-e2nds3&quot;&gt;Exploring Lightning Network Routing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_099 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_099---Announcing-C-Lightning-0-6-e2ndrh&quot;&gt;Announcing C-Lightning 0.6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_136 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_136---The-Panama-Canal-and-The-Bitcoin-Lightning-Network-e2ndq9&quot;&gt;The Panama Canal and The Bitcoin Lightning Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_139 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_139---Lightning-Network-2-0-Part1-e2ndq7&quot;&gt;Lightning Network 2.0 [Part1]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_140 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_140---Lightning-Network-2-0-Part-2-e2ndq6&quot;&gt;Lightning Network 2.0 [Part 2]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_142 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_142---Chaincodes-Residency-Program-Is-Back--This-Time-With-Lightning-e2ndq3&quot;&gt;Chaincode’s Residency Program Is Back, This Time With Lightning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;GuysTake_002 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/GuysTake_002---The-Lightning-App-I-Want-to-Use-e2ndp6&quot;&gt;The Lightning App I Want to Use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_169 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_169---Neutrino-The-Lighter-Side-of-Lightning-e2ndp4&quot;&gt;Neutrino: The Lighter Side of Lightning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_183 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_183---Custody-in-the-Age-of-Digital-Assets-e2ndoi&quot;&gt;Custody in the Age of Digital Assets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_199 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_199---Confidential-Auditing-by-Nick-Szabo-e2oqkk&quot;&gt;Confidential Auditing by Nick Szabo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_200 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_200---Why-Bitcoins-Lightning-Network-is-Ingenious-e2plij&quot;&gt;Why Bitcoin’s Lightning Network is Ingenious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoChat_008 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoChat_008---Under-the-Lightning-Hood-with-petoveritas--Crypt0PuraVida---CoinBeezy-e2q4gf&quot;&gt;Under the Lightning Hood with @petoveritas, @Crypt0PuraVida, &amp;amp; @CoinBeezy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_206 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_206---Reckless-to-Wumbology--The-Lightning-Network-Infrastructural-Build-Out-e3235m&quot;&gt;#Reckless to Wumbology, The Lightning Network Infrastructural Build-Out&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;GuysTake_008 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/GuysTake_008---The-Lightning-of-my-TCP--or-How-the-Internet-is-Too-Complex-to-Work-e32omd&quot;&gt;The Lightning of my TCP, or How the Internet is Too Complex to Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoChat_009 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoChat_009---Holding-the-Lightning-Torch-on-the-Rollo--Slappy-Show-e36t53&quot;&gt;Holding the Lightning Torch on the Rollo &amp;amp; Slappy Show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoChat_011 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoChat_011---Lightning--Paywall-Link---the-Bootstrap-Bandit-e3smfp&quot;&gt;Lightning, Paywall.Link, &amp;amp; the Bootstrap Bandit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;GuysTake_011 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/GuysTake_011---Why-Lightning-Sucks-e3r95t&quot;&gt;Why Lightning Sucks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;GuysTake_014 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/GuysTake_014---The-What--Why---How-of-Lightning-e41pbe&quot;&gt;The What, Why, &amp;amp; How of Lightning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_248 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_248---Bitrefills-Hottest-Lightning-Tech-of-2019-e426ph&quot;&gt;Bitrefill’s Hottest Lightning Tech of 2019!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_259 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_259---Lightning-at-the-End-of-the-Tunnel-e4a35k&quot;&gt;Lightning at the End of the Tunnel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h3 id=&quot;lapps&quot;&gt;LApps&lt;/h3&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dev.lightning.community/lapps/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/qs08w40.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuickRead_031.5 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuickRead_031-5---Lapp-1---FileBazaar-e2ndts&quot;&gt;Lapp 1 - FileBazaar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_032.5 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_032-5---Lapp-2---Lightning-Publisher-e2ndtq&quot;&gt;Lapp 2 - Lightning Publisher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_033.5 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_033-5---LApp-3---NanoTip-e2ndto&quot;&gt;LApp 3 - NanoTip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_034.5 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_034-5---LApp-4---PayPerCall-e2ndtm&quot;&gt;LApp 4 - PayPerCall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_035.5 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_035-5---LApp-5---Nanopos-for-Simple-Point-of-Sale-e2ndtk&quot;&gt;LApp 5 - Nanopos for Simple Point-of-Sale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_036.5 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_036-5---LApp-6---Ifpaytt-Brings-Lightning-Payments-to-IFTTT-e2ndth&quot;&gt;LApp 6 - Ifpaytt Brings Lightning Payments to IFTTT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_037.5 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_037-5---Lapp-7---The-Lightning-Jukebox-e2ndti&quot;&gt;Lapp 7 - The Lightning Jukebox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;h2 id=&quot;related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/security/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Security Info + Best Practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assorted Technical Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/privacy/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy and Bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/lightning/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin - Layer 2 - Lightning, Liquid and Beyond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-1/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Layer 1 - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/decentralization/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li class=&quot;text-right&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/feed/archive/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More ›&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;


  
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/layer-2/lightning/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Bitcoin - Layer 2 - Lightning, Liquid and Beyond</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/layer-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;small-12 columns&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;panel radius&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 21px;&quot;&gt;
			&lt;a class=&quot;button left r15 tiny radius&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-layer-2.md&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top: 3px;&quot;&gt;
			This content is open source.
			&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bitcoinfo/bitcoinfo.github.io/blob/master/_posts/tech/2019-12-29-layer-2.md&quot;&gt;Help improve it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_093 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_093---The-Importance-of-Layer-2-e2ndrp&quot;&gt;The Importance of Layer 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_132 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_132---The-Bitcoin-Second-Layer-e2ndqd&quot;&gt;The Bitcoin Second Layer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_022 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_022---Sidechains---Why-These-Researchers-Think-They-Solved-a-Key-Piece-of-the-Puzzle-e2ndu6&quot;&gt;Sidechains - Why These Researchers Think They Solved a Key Piece of the Puzzle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;-liquid&quot;&gt;🚧 Liquid&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://elementsproject.org/how-it-works&quot;&gt;elementsproject.org/how-it-works&lt;/a&gt;
Elements - an open source, sidechain-capable blockchain platform.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Blockstream/liquid&quot;&gt;Blockstream/liquid&lt;/a&gt; - Liquid daemon and cli.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ElementsProject/elements&quot;&gt;ElementsProject/elements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/hackernoon/getting-started-with-the-liquid-network-c87e2cb5996b&quot;&gt;Getting started with the Liquid Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/blockstream/getting-started-with-lightning-on-the-liquid-network-8b5682752ffe&quot;&gt;Getting started with Lighning on the Liquid Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_166 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_166---Liquid-Network-Launch-and-Thoughts-from-LucasNuzzi-e2ndp8&quot;&gt;Liquid Network Launch and Thoughts from @LucasNuzzi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CryptoQuikRead_167 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/thecryptoconomy/episodes/CryptoQuikRead_167---Deep-Dive-into-Strong-Federations--Foundations-of-Liquid-e2ndp7&quot;&gt;Deep Dive into Strong Federations &amp;amp; Foundations of Liquid&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-bitcoin-knowledge-podcast/id301670981?mt=2&amp;amp;i=1000429693505&quot;&gt;Legendary guest Dr. Adam Back updates his Bitcoin observations. The Bitcoin Knowledge Podcast&lt;/a&gt; «&amp;lt;good overview lightning and liquid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Legendary guest Dr. Adam Back, cofounder and CEO of Blockstream, gives his latest observations of the Bitcoin ecosystem.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theblockcrypto.com/2018/10/17/crypto-simplified-explaining-sidechains/&quot;&gt;Crypto Simplified: Explaining Sidechains - The Block&lt;/a&gt;
The launch of Blockstream’s Liquid Network brings with it a resurgence of questions surrounding sidechains. As with everything we do here at The Block we are going to take a “Crypto Simplified” approach at explaining sidechains. What are sidechains? In simplest terms, s…
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/BlockstreamHelp/status/1159210378255110150?s=20&quot;&gt;Blockstream Help (@BlockstreamHelp)&lt;/a&gt;
Liquid is temporarily unavailable due to a scheduled upgrade that requires additional functionary action. This upgrade will complete in the next 12 hours. All funds in Liquid are secure during this outage. We apologize for any inconvenience.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/francescoppola/2018/10/11/blockstreams-new-solution-to-bitcoins-liquidity-problem-looks-oddly-familiar/&quot;&gt;Blockstream’s New Solution To Bitcoin’s Liquidity Problem Looks Od…&lt;/a&gt;
Blockstream’s Liquid sidechain purports to be an innovative solution to Bitcoin’s chronic illiquidity. But it inadvertently replicates something with which we are all too familiar.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/blockstreams-liquid-network-high-value-bitcoin-payments-live/&quot;&gt;Blockstream’s Liquid Network for “High Value” Bitcoin Paymen…&lt;/a&gt;
Blockstream’s COO Samson Mow explains how “Liquid is designed to facilitate fast and reliable high value transfers” of bitcoin (and other cryptocurrencies – eventually.)
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Truthcoin/status/1044744031824015360&quot;&gt;Paul Sztorc (@Truthcoin)&lt;/a&gt;
Yes, it is true! You can now run our testnet, and send BTC to and from the first P2P sidechain: “Sidechain One”. We will have LargeBlock and HugeBlock sidechains up soon, and of course the super-alpha of my futarchy project @BitcoinHivemind !! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/bitcoin-just-took-a-step-toward-becoming-a-multi-network-cryptocurrency&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Takes a Step Toward Becoming a ‘Multi-Network’ Cryptocurrency&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/messarinews/status/1173652436592005120?s=12&quot;&gt;Messari News (@MessariNews)&lt;/a&gt;
Bull Bitcoin joins Blockstream’s Liquid exchange network &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/lGyIh46gs7&quot;&gt;https://t.co/lGyIh46gs7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;drivechain&quot;&gt;Drivechain&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.drivechain.info/&quot;&gt;drivechain.info&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.drivechain.info/blog/first-release/&quot;&gt;Drivechain Release Announcement&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bitcoin.com/drivechain-project-sees-an-influx-of-development-since-launch&quot;&gt;Drivechain Project Sees an Influx of Development Since Launch - Bi…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Software developer Paul Sztorc revealed on Sept. 24 the launch of his first iteration of Drivechain, a sidechain concept that enables a cross-chain Since Drivechain has launched, the project has added a slew of sidechain tools and another chain that resembles the Bitcoin Cash…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rootstock&quot;&gt;Rootstock&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rootstock.io/&quot;&gt;rootstock.io&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;RSK, bitcoin´s smart contract platform.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rsksmart/tutorials/wiki&quot;&gt;rsksmart/tutorials/wiki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoin.stackexchange.com/questions/54036/can-someone-show-me-an-example-rootstock-smart-contract-that-is-the-equivalent-o&quot;&gt;Can someone show me an example rootstock smart contract that is th…&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Coming from Ethereum, is there an example rootstock smart contract code that is the equivalent of an Ethereum smart contract code?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rsksmart/tutorials/wiki&quot;&gt;rsksmart/tutorials&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Tutorials about how to get started coding for RSK. 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/sdlerner/status/1075506026114371584?s=12&quot;&gt;Sergio Demian Lerner (@SDLerner)&lt;/a&gt;
After reading @AaronvanW ‘s excellent review of Bitcoin and @RSKSmart growth in 2018, I decided do provide actual statistics of RSK growth in 2018 .. so here is the tweet thread !&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/JWWeatherman_/status/1069232488604729344&quot;&gt;JW Weatherman - mathbot.com (@JWWeatherman_)&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;#rsk #rootstock https://t.co/dmwA7j7U3K Is still planning to introduce a security flaw they call “drive chains” If they get enough fools to put bitcoin on this flawed side chain it will resulting a massive theft of #bitcoin Defend bitcoin by alerting people of the …&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;related-posts&quot;&gt;Related Posts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/security/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Security Info + Best Practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assorted Technical Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/info/privacy/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy and Bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/lightning/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-2/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin - Layer 2 - Lightning, Liquid and Beyond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/layer-1/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Layer 1 - Info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/tech/decentralization/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    
      &lt;li class=&quot;text-right&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/feed/archive/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More ›&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;


  
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/layer-2/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
